Just a small betrayal
A mirror's edge and the heart's parade
You drew your truth in silent lines
Symbols bleeding through the veil
Lost taste in like red berries
But if we just have to look, there's always a crack in the cold
Don't stare straight, look sideways
23 people here already. Thank you so much for being here. Look, I'll dress it up to me.
Okay, how are we doing? Yo, Elias, how are you? Burning joint, everyone's here, the whole gang is
Thank you. I do have like a lot more of the nightbot command set up if you want to check out
the link that came up when I did exclamation point commands. That will take you to all the
commands and there's some cool ones in there. Some cool ones in there. How are we doing?
Here's a round of my cats tonight. Oh my gosh. Well yeah, it looks pretty good. I like how it looks
The question is what am I wearing under this, you know, I don't know, I don't know if we'll be able to figure out tonight, but maybe I'll show you.
Let me see, need to get my invite link up. Hello, Nick.
Hi guys.
Yeah, they're goodbyes only one.
There should be one. Okay, I'll let my bot know.
Page requested a special Nightbot command. I'm going to put that one in there. Good vibes.
I do have the butt plug and butthole. I think they might be still there. I think they're still there.
Okay, how are we doing? Okay.
We're doing an incense thing tonight. I have some incense.
I do.
I can do a little innocent ritual, a little smoky, get a little smoky, okay, let's do
it.
Okay, so let me see, where's my, okay, I have that, I have my, any charcoal, where's my
charcoal?
Oh, this charcoal's not even burned out.
Let's see if I can get that burning.
Okay.
I have these really I got this really cool kit like a years ago, and I never even used it. It's like so cool. It has all the planetary
incense blends
See if I can get this working
It should spark up if it works
This might be burned out though
I think this one's burned out. Okay, just defined
Find another one, well, I know I have like a whole box in my room we get up
They're having some okay
So these are like charcoal there you go, huh? There you go
Age let's age. Okay, so here I have these charcoal masters
Light them up. What's up guys 27 people here. Wow. This is like I might have my other channel. Let's say had a shadow band on it because I
Never this I never got that. Thank you guys for being here
Oh
You can spam but look everywhere
Second but so let's see the new lights up. Oh, no, there you go. See it's the most
Berkeley
See it
That's pretty cool. Okay before I get burned. Oh look what we have here
Hello
Hello, how are you? I'm okay. I'm still blinking your breathing. How are you?
Oh, yeah, it's not breathing. I'm still blinking
Yeah, well, we can't say that but you know what will seem so I suppose could be worse could be better
It'd be worth could be better, right? So what what day is it? It's Thursday. So it's the Thursday. So Thursday is what Jupiter?
doors like Jupiter.
I think so, yeah.
So I have these like little like canisters of these instances and
Oh, are they like like days of the week burners like days of the week underwear?
Yeah, well, these are like planetary plus. There's elemental ones too. So there's like air wind fire water too, but there's all the planets
Yeah, I love that. Where'd you get it? I got it from there's a guy named Shudd
Jason Augustus Nucombe, he's like a magician. He's a really talented magician. He makes a lot of a lot of products, too
There you go. Oh, that's awesome. And so this is a good
Way to get these like benefit benefit sent planetary energy. I have this one. This one is a spirit. I guess this is the spirit
You can do some spirit
Yeah, spirit one. These are the really nice like little powdery
Okay, yeah, it's almost like a loose incense in a sense, like yeah
And I just kind of just kind of just a little tiny little pinch of it and I like sprinkle it on the charcoal
And then it comes up and all these good stuff will happen all this good stuff happen
Yeah, I'm gonna I'm putting more ritual into the show because it's a cult, you know
So it's gonna have like some more ritual, but no, this is an interesting cult. It's the only one. Oh, you're banned
No, you're not banned say I see your comment. This is the only a
This is the only a cult that has actually a fish taco prophecy
But only the highest level members will receive that one, but
Once you hear the truth about fish tacos, you'll probably never get the same again. Oh my gosh
You're talking to me like I don't know like I'm brand new
Oh, yeah, you know, oh, you probably you know some of the fish, but this it's a little bit
Yeah, I've reworked some of it, but I really do have a lot of really cool stuff. I've written up. There's over like a
Probably 60 page manual. I put with like a lot of like the teachings and everything. It's got all my astrology
And it's pretty cool and in the website, too
Oh my god, there you go. Yeah. Oh my god. The website is looking good. I'm just like I had to Reese kind of
Rework it a little bit. I don't know if the old one's still up. I might have to read transfer to the new page, but
It's gonna have everything on there
It's got the membership there, so I don't have the membership on YouTube anymore
But I have it through there and there's a five dollar one like there was here
Basically the same benefits there, but then on the $10 and $20 tears you do get like a either a 15 minute or 30 minute phone call with me
You can talk about anything from getting a terror reading or
talking about your
your channel or your social media presence or
AI or you know, I know a lot of stuff. I know a lot of stuff and so whatever whatever
I think that that will definitely make it worth it to have the personal phone call
And so plus you can get the higher, higher level information stuff.
So I'm designing it so it's cool for everybody.
I'm also going to put a, I've designed a tarot app to put on the page too,
where it's like you can get a really good tarot reading just, you know,
for free on there through that.
It's a pretty cool program I made.
So cool stuff going on.
You're being on stream yard sick. Okay. I'll check my stream here. What's going on page? How are you?
I'm okay. I'm just doing some artwork just trying to busy my mind, you know, so don't fall into the
Even crazier crazy of my you know, you know the flux and the flow of all the shit. I just uh trying to
uh-huh every hurt every injured myself. Uh-oh, so I'm trying to did all that healing for kind of nothing now
So what part did you injure on my hip and my feet like I my hip again? I put my hip out again really bad
SIG are you Larry Nash on a on the?
On the stream yard, that's I think that's your name. I just took I just I'm really fun to hit you because
You know at sig sig would always like, you know, just break the to us, but I'm not like not concerned about to us anymore
Even if this channel gets goes down. I do have another backup channel plus
I have like streams on kick and twitch and so if you follow my
The website it'll be live streaming through there, too. And so it's like you can always find me
Plus sign up for the mailing list too so I can just update you. I'm not gonna like spam you or anything
I'm gonna send good. I'm gonna send just very good interesting stuff, you know, I'm
Wanting this to be fun for everybody and and they're good for everybody plus my cult is like 50% completely serious
And then it's like 30%
It's 30% what about how do I say it 30% like a satire I go like a satire of a cool and then
20% I kind of a troll but I think it's there. I think it's still fun for everybody. Okay, so plus
I'll get all the stuff like trollopedia everything everything readings through there and everything so it's like just
That'll be a good community hub
and uh, yeah, I'm taking I'm taking the
negative
And then turning into positive. That's alchemy guys
called
I'm transmuting it transmuting the energy and you can it's like and it's like just the bad things that can happen
You can make them gold, you know, you can you can turn like the shit into gold
That's that's the real alchemy these to turn like lead into gold
You can actually turn shit into gold and that's like, you know, then I can open a fertilizer factory
I already got the idea from all these bags of fertilizer. I was getting put on my
Yeah, what
You guys remember the old days when shit was like you like, you know
Like when I was climbing on the roof and like when other things like just those days those were good
Those are good times and you know what? Oh, yeah. Well, let's get back to those. I mean, yeah
It was like an innocent time it's like going back to your childhood is like impossible to do
But you can remember it and it's like and then you can like kind of like be silly still
But, you know, there'll never be some of the same people around, and, you know, relationships
will change through time, and it's sad.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
It's just good memories as well.
Yeah.
And unfortunately, like, you know, a lot of those memories, you know, were just deleted
by YouTube, because, you know, anything that wasn't on Rumble.
is, you know, syndicated by Livestream VOD or Livestream,
I think that's his name, anybody that,
all those streams are probably gone forever.
But, oh, and look, we have Will Wickers here.
Let's welcome Will Wickers.
What do you think?
Does Will Wickers, oh, it's SIG.
They go are you it's been a different haircut. Did you know Joker had a mohawk today?
And I said hi to him and I was like too cool to say hi now
Mohawk's got in your head
It was pretty cute. I'm to say I was like jumpers at most
I know I can't know I'm in love with I'm in love with I'm sorry. He's 20 he's 25 years old like I'm sorry
I know I know he's too young for me, but I don't know I can do this like fantasize a little bit. What are you doing, Ziggy?
Drinking yeah me too. You're drinking. I'm not drinking. I'm just smoking a little bit
I'm smoking math, and I'm dreaming. Oh my god, SIG please don't... SIG!
These are things that people do, you know what I mean?
Don't do that on my stream. Well, don't be that way, SIG, you know?
Please do it off camera. Not publicly, yeah, I was just gonna say.
Nah, just do this shit for fun, you know what I mean?
Are you okay though? Like do you need to make some usually people on meadow a little bit more? No, I don't need any like medical attention
I feel like I'm chilling. Okay. Well, if you do
Yeah, I'm chilling. Okay. See like what's this guy's name?
Father's a guy on the top left. Oh father's thank you
Call me father, call me father, this individual psyche, you have like people banned in your
stream, you know what I mean?
You have me ban on your streamer had to log into a different account
Yeah, you might have to like clear your balance or something people do
I'm not gonna clear the balance because there's people with terrible terrible names and most of them are porn bombers
So why would I clear the balance? Well, that's the thing. That's the thing psyche
Let me just say this right don't shoot the messenger
Don't shoot the messenger what people do on that are streamers, right? Yeah, generally
What streamers do is that every so often they will clear the ban list. I understand the ban list
But that's mainly understand ban list not the streamer ban list where it's like streamer ban list
It was like no general. No, it's a general everyone
Generally
I know they're bad people I can read you some of the names like listen to these names that are on my ban list
I mean, I don't know
Nugget service. We have mr. Trouble. He sounds like trouble Mando Garmento Mersal Rudolph has these are all porn bombers Roger Klotz. Is that you?
Are you Roger Roger Klotz?
Amanda huggy kid
We have already artsy flanners petty wop. It doesn't sound like a nice person. Are you Flanders? This is really funny
Stop stop me
I don't think it's the real Theo gate though. I mean, Yoko the clown 2.0.
These are all really funny names. I'm sorry.
John Kavanaugh, Darth Vader first ever seen, Big Daddy, Time Bomb, Bala Bann.
And I don't know, that's a pretty much. And so I think that most of them are...
Okay, unless you heard your name there, then I'm not gonna know I don't think any of can you say oh again?
40 people in the chat. Whoa guys. Whoa. Come on the chat. It's the chat
That's the that's the signals. That's the signal 66 effect
Six six. Oh, yeah, I think it's a page effect me. That's the signal 66 effect in the fact
All right, figure it out sleep at night Ziggy
Yeah, I sleep better knowing that Paige didn't just say that and so now I'm gonna sleep bad tonight
You're fine
What I mean
Powers to create nightmares
Yeah, I can do that. I can do that yet. Well, I had I had some interesting dreams last night one of them
I was like
I let like a panther in but it was like it was kind of like a shape-shifting panther where it was like and it was like
Kind of like I didn't know if other people could see it and then like they could now
I was like kind of wrestling with it, but it was like real it was real friendly and
That was one of the better dreams because like I said, yeah, I told Pace today
Panther was one of my totems when I dream about it
That means well, yeah
I remember I brought it up because I pulled that card last night and it was for Alexander
But then my internet and so I had to like I couldn't read the card
But I didn't really say it was for him because he wasn't up there.
He was in the back doing whatever he was having a little fit.
Yeah, but anyways, so it was like I then I brought that up today
Cuz it's how random that you know that would hide it's not random
But like it does sync up
But it was neat to bring that up and I was like hey psych you should read that out of our
Animal spirit guidebook and then he didn't he went on the internet. He found this other cool like totem. Ouch. I'm stuck in my pajamas
Okay, anyways totem is like information and it was really cool, too
But then I read when I got off your live psych. I read the
information card. No, yeah, yeah, and it was really, really cool too. So anyways, all of it
correlated and it was really neat. And, you know, sometimes things connect. So just pay
attention to that because you could have a message in it for you.
Well, yeah, and I mean, I mean, I know Black Panther was a kind of a radical organization too
But really does have anything to do with race. Yeah, actually and I what I learned today, too
It's like there's not really such thing as a black panther
They're main they're actually just like leopards with like a with actually like a like a genetic thing where they're all black
Or Jaguar or even they said any big cat that's all black, you know, they can call it a black panther. Hey, Jamie's Cowboys
How are you doing?
why is your sleep schedule messed up KZ the homie I don't know what's going on with you
hey guys we also have the discord um is up and running I have a permanent link now to it but
I will put the link now actually I think it should be um programmed into the nightbot let me check
wow I got the nightbot the link I am would you say asalaamu alaykum asalaam alaykum
We're speaking. I'm basically I
Basically used to fuck this Arab whore
I don't know if she didn't really like me but her parents did
W
Hopefully, I don't know. It's not musically ricks or you don't know. Okay. No, it's a greeting. It's a saying
That's not a nice greeting
Yeah, it is work on your like greetings. I think a little bit
It's something like a peace be with you and you know some God God be with you
That's fucked up, what do you mean that's fucked up. It's actually a kind thing to say to someone
Well, also, I'm like, it's all point. That's a lot more like them
Okay, let's see. I'm gonna get to my
I need to my live and I'm gonna post the live in a few places. Maybe we'll get some more people here
But if we get a hundred people here tonight guys, I'm lifting up my my my
I'm just gonna lift it up and show you what if you get a hundred viewers if he gets a hundred viewers
He's gonna show everybody his vagina
Everybody get excited get excited
Okay, I'm going to post my, my discourse and maybe the discourse people will show up. I have a few
discords I'm on that, uh, I don't know why I'm hearing repeating. There we go. Okay, there we go.
Actually, I think many people liked my thumbnail. I think I have a pretty good thumbnail tonight.
Let me see.
I can post it in joker's well you know what it doesn't matter why psych it just matters that people are here and we all like it just just let it flow just let it happen naturally well I'm just like really thankful because I've let it happen I'm letting it happen but I've just let it happen let it happen okay but I'm saying I've been to like see you're yelling and then you're saying it just you're saying you're letting it happen but you're not letting happens like he just like what it
calm down let it happen
I'm like a woman
No, no except except you're not a woman though because you're a man like you know you're a feminine man
I mean, I just saw your message page page has okay. I'm not going to tell her to calm down
Jamie what I need to apologize for I sent her two messages
You asked me to send her yeah
And I was very polite in the messages and she told me to basically go fuck myself and jump off of a bridge
I'm over the wall. Why do I have to apologize for Jamie? Just let me know if I did something to her
I'm willing to hear it out. What have you tried jumping off a bridge?
Well, you know, it's like if it's not too, too, too, I'm just getting pretty evident
He didn't because he's still here and he
I mean, there's yeah, it's like it was like I can got the joke so he got there again
Like a he jumped and maybe he jumped off of a five inch bridge
Little like London bridge, you know, it's just right into the water
He would have told us about it. He told us about his dream. Let's see. Do we guys want do we want to tell you?
Yeah, what you're saying doesn't make sense and I disagree
Are you talking to me or Paige?
Paige, okay. How does what I just said not make any sense. It's logical. It's fucksig
No, I disagree look at your little smirk. You know that you're just you're just fucking with me
What do you mean though? I'm just saying that I disagree
With what you were saying
Okay, he would he would share it with I disagree with what you were saying because I don't even know what you were saying
That's why I'm smirking
Because I forgot in all honesty right I forgot what you were saying
Okay, I don't even know what you were saying or discussing. I'm not on the same page at all
Okay, no, no, no hold on hold on hold on. I'm not done
What I'm saying is none the less
Nonetheless, I
Still know I disagree with what you were saying
Well, stop just okay, even though even though I don't remember
Even though I don't remember I don't
I what I remember what I remember is that I disagree
So you're just wasting our time. Let me come on. Let's look like again. This sounds like a you problem
No, this isn't this is not a me problem. No, I'm getting I'm separating you and page of you guys are fighting too much
Okay, no fighting. Hey, I mean a psyche. How do you see things with your sunglasses on?
In darkness, I'm not in darkness. First of all, these are just tinted glasses. Basically. They're just like a light
You can see my eyes perfectly. Can you why do you look like Jeffrey Dahmer?
I don't I don't it was he a Catholic priest
This is my this is my cult leader outfit
Do you have the Nike marathons?
No, because I think Nike's is racist name
I'm just kidding. I don't know. It's not really. Okay. Um, let me see. Did I get... Oh, you got indoctrinated by the Palestinians I see regulations. Okay, okay. I don't want to get into the Middle East. I don't, I don't know how. I don't want to get into... Okay. You know, fair enough. I don't want to get into these.
Panties on and I'd like that get on my knees for Colin Kaepernick
Person I don't even believe in I don't believe in Colin Kaepernick. I think that was a
That was a we can tell I voted I voted for Colin Kaepernick
It's like capper like a caper and Nick like my son
I don't believe in that person. I think that was a
Psyop, but we don't have to discuss that. Maybe that's me personally. I voted for Colin Kaepernick
Well, he's a murderer. I mean, he's pretending. Why would you vote for him? He's a murderer of people in the college or something
What are you talking about? Is that what Colin Kaepernick did? No, what the hell? I don't know. I'm talking about the NFL player. Oh
The Colin Kaepernick. Oh, I don't know what you're thinking. Well, maybe I'm just confused
You're gay, so you're not supposed to know those things
No, I do know I do know something
They Mar Hamlin, do you know who DeMar Hamlin is anybody? No
Don't know about fucking shooters. Okay, the bar Hamlin's actually a football player not a shooter
Okay, he was a football player
He had a heart attack a cardiac arrest on the playing field and then alright, then he kind of like
Started to come and showing up to games like all like hidden in all his bases. I'm not gonna blame you Jamie
I'm not please. I don't want you to get me. I'll say I'll say out of it
I don't want you to have any more problems. Just enjoy your relationship. I shouldn't be gone. Malvin in the first place
I told you it's like this bitch it give her give her the blame. She wants it
She's begging for doesn't he doesn't want it. She doesn't want it. She would not like she wants it
Jamie I don't I'm gonna blame Jamie's the top mod here. She's the top mods. She doesn't get I'll take the blame
It was my fault. Just tell it was my fault. I'm the dick. Of course. I'm the dick, you know
Well, we don't need to talk about these unhappy things. We're talking pages here. We're talking about positivity
It's kind of tell positivity page Thursday. I like that
Positivity page for you know page is like one of the
The goddesses my cult will call them goddesses, right? She one of the goddesses of the cult
You used to be called psyches beauties in them previously before that psyches angels
Say a psyches angels is trademark. You couldn't use them
That was trademarked by me though
So yes, I mean a Charles angels trademark
But it's psyche's angels. I'm not that that was Charlie's angels. I was using that. Yes, that'd be trademark issue
But it's the same thing
No, psyche's angels are different. My angels are not like, you know, Daryl Hannah and you know, whoever the other two blonde bitches were
I mean, I'm not
Ladies
Beautiful ladies angels the angels. I mean, they were I mean, there's that Asian girl
Oh, there's an Asian angel, so Lucy Lou. Oh my god. She wasn't blonde
She was not from the 70s. She was probably 12 years old when that was out in the 70s
No, I'm talking about Charlie's Angels. Oh the movie newer one. Yeah
TV show called Charlie's Angels in the 70s that that movie was based on saying you don't know about that
Where are you? Oh, you don't know that? Okay. There's actually a mass before my time in the 70s
I mean, I'm not like fucking 40 years old, dude.
Fucks sake.
Shout out to you, dude.
I mean, I haven't seen.
How are we doing, guys, in chat?
You're like, man, bong.
Look at this.
This is the bong.
Easy got me.
It's still very vibrant.
Look at it.
That's a cute guy.
Say, do you want to kiss?
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
Put your head to the side and kiss.
I mean, I think I would I think I would want physical contact
more like
Yeah, I mean with me. Oh, goodness
This with this face
How about with 300 glow and me? Can we do that man in 300 glow on me? I can't speak for somebody else's consent
Yeah, what do you think he would do? He's he seemed open to it last time
I don't know. It's possible. It's possible that I could bring him up. Okay. Is that what you'd want? Yes, please do that
He's cool. Actually, I like I don't I think he's cool. I like him too. Yeah, I think I think page page was like
300 glow is telling me that like page was like
Saying that he's all sexy and shit. No, I never said that and I was wearing my blonde wig
You know so like yeah, ww 300 glow. I mean, that's my boy right there
That's not even facts
Look you wear the ski mask and can you wear a wife beater and then my dreams would come true for the night
No, and then I don't I don't own white beaters. You don't no, I don't own white beaters
How about a tank top I don't want to take
How about just oh, I don't own a tank top. I just have a tank on top of me
You know what we're gonna do with this psyche, you know
I don't want that inside me. Can we put a condom on it first?
Why now are you are you confused because the page and I are both these beautiful blondes? What do you think?
Yeah, I can't even tell the difference. I can't tell the difference
Look oh
I don't know. Yeah, put the pineapple away. I'm feeling blow. Please. I might I might
Hey guys, you know Hawaii actually is not where pineapples come from they just like turn into a big pineapple farm
Pineapples are actually from like the East. Oh, I'm missing something. Let me show my team pineapples are where from the fuck
I want them to be
Look what my girl copy
Hey, Baclips.
Look who my girl got.
Hey, is it a toy?
What is it?
Feaker?
Lights?
It's a ring light.
Yeah.
My girl got me.
He puts that whole shit up his ass.
It's a ring light.
He didn't know.
You know, thank you for visiting my TikTok.
How are you?
That's all I got to say today.
Thank you so much.
Appreciate that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well.
Well, she got that for herself 300 globe, but then you can use it, you know, it's nice for me for real
That's a nice. I have this one, but it's like in the way. I needed like a tall one
You know me I'm trying to look pretty on here the fuck
What you do, you're gorgeous. Thank you. But you know what would be scary if you and you or SIG and drag would be really
horrifying
I'm a smoke meth like my last name is bad
Please don't say good. It's not very good for you
You might lose a few pounds. That's the one I see now one more
Don't do it. I'm a smoke man. Just don't my last name is Keith
just don't smoke anything
Soon enough, I'm gonna lose all my teeth
Yeah, you do that probably big destiny. I'm gonna start rapping and trapping
Cuz this little signals capping. That's not too shabby
So guys we have a I'm gonna be on the block and I'm gonna keep
With the Glock 9
There's no signal send me my friends don't know today and it was 10 bucks or something
Alexander McQueen Alexander McQueen NYPD
I think I said I need two seconds
But I'm gonna give him like four seconds
I don't know what's up with my sexy police officer. Hey, Alex, I met a real cop last night. This cop came on for like 10 minutes and he was
He said, he said, how do I look? Do I look better than the woman? I was like, yeah, the chauffeur show
I got all excited and shit. That was your first mistake. Look what I can do with my tongue
He got all excited. He was like, damn
You look like a crazy artist for like the 50s, like you hang out with Andy Warhol or something.
It's a little bit Andy Warhol.
He's saying you look like Stanley Kubrick's friends.
Oh yeah.
He's hooked up.
We like you about the flight.
I can you look like you about to suck off a bunch of gay dudes
I'm wearing under my frock
No, hopefully you're g-shing my man, hopefully the American flag
Cash app maybe I'll show everybody
It's a fish net. It's a fish net a fish net. Okay. Well, you're rock. You're wrong. I'm not wearing fish
That's good. Look my legs. My legs are like amazing. Can you see them?
Oh my fucking god, I just want to take the time right now to thank signal for sending my first donation
On my channel
Who don't fucking skating
Leave Katie alone. I don't even know who Katie is baby. There we go. Look at those chicken legs. Look at those chicken legs
Those are like ostrich legs
Those are ostrich legs, I do but you know someone someone actually I talked to on the phone
I have sexy legs. She said
That's why you get no pussy
Wait, wait, wait, hold on, Saiki, Saiki, you're like 6'4", right?
3'6'3".
You lessen her seat?
I have to lie.
I have to hear her legs.
You got to mute your mic.
You only got to mute your mic.
Fuckin' retouch.
Like, you're lying.
Those on your legs.
300 gloves give me his girlfriend.
No, no, no.
He bought that at a party city.
Because I seen him bent over in the D string, the American flag, and he had need on the
I still have to be on my phone.
That was all bones, dude.
300, you gotta hit the mute button, stupid ass.
Wait, 300, how'd you get fucking doors on your cabinets?
Overnight, my man.
Overnight?
Yeah, you were at summer class and I was making fun of you like you have no fucking door to your cabinets and now you have doors
Hucked them up with a bunch of beaners no offense
Oh
Hey, let me see your bullet hole
That's gonna be my snack
We got me hit the link Jamie's cowboy at the link and explain to me who the fuck is
Here's my show. All right, let's drink. Let's drink
Then you'll feel like it you'll feel like showing you guys either
I have alcohol actually, but I have a coffee too, but I'm we'll whip it out and so
But I never know when you know last day's gonna be it will be shots
Celebrate like
Yes, 52 inch. Yeah, let's go. Yes
LFG let's fucking go. I mean this guy this guy Alex this guy Alex is like a bitch
You know me he got shot
And that's why he is off duty. You know what I mean? God bless him. He served his city
Because he like, you know, I mean god bless him
He's off duty
Yeah
And he was like he had a military
Oh, that's so cool
That's so funny wait, then he's saying he was what the fuck
I know
I'm my best friend's a cop
Thank you, all right, baby, can you see why you're out there bitch
Okay guys we get to a hundred
Like you know some donations
There's a cabinet overnight
We want to go take that off your face take a human condom off your face
Take off your shirt
Please
Take the human turn the man. I can't get it. I can't get a ban on rumble. You know, that's why you can't look it will wake
Or saying about the hurl
I'm holding what yeah, you can that the dude Aldi one can I know what he did he got himself in
Yeah, ban on rumble. Well, he's
Everyone just wants to
What is on your chin there's something on your chin according on your chinny chin chin my chin
The whisked your facial hair. Oh my god, that's a special hair
He glued it on he's on the run they're both on the run obviously
safe changes for all appearance and look at the guy with the fucking mask on
I changed my appearance by cutting my fucking hair
I want to get my hair done bro
there are a pair of criminals ISIS looking for them
there's probably a reward out
people are saying looking for me
are you a person
Will wickers or
I hope I hope the I hope ISIS ain't looking for me with the fuck
I
Know Navajo nation he looks like he's missing from like some Indian camp right from a restoration
He looks like he should be Moana. I'm a fucking American
They go looks like he's planning a fucking bank robbery
Probably you probably just got back from one. Can you can I see the cash stacks and the in the in the ink pack?
Please I'll show you something else. I see the die
I'm gonna see if you want to go backstage. I'll end the show right now. I don't care if there's 50 people in here
I want to see
So he's crazy
So he wants to see you naked
Three you're glows seen me naked I think
Yeah, I have
I've never seen
Oh
Thank you. Is your wife laughing. Oh, yeah, okay good. Hi wifey
Hola esposa. She can't hear you. Okay. I'm sorry
We'll tell her Kato. She said hi
Okay, hola, hola
You only speak Spanish
Well, yeah, she only speak Guatemalans. She don't speak Spanish
Don't speak cracker
¿Puedes poner tus bolas en mi boca?
¿Puedes poner tus bolas en tu boca?
Yo voy a poner un reloj en tu huevo.
¿Puedes poner un reloj en tu huevo?
Poner un reloj en tus huevos
You want to put a watch in my bowl
Yo quiero no yo quiero mirar
that's what he said, I want to go to watch in your balls
crazy
he wants to watch your balls
no, no, not watch, or watch, like, take talk
yo, yo, voy a poner un perlo en tu madre
what do you mean? don't talk about people's mothers
that's so rude to talk about people's mothers
no, I'm not talking about your mother
no, it's a saying, it's a slang
It's not
Anybody's mother. No, it's not it's not the literal mother. You don't you're not understanding
If this guy is really NYPD, he knows what I'm talking about
When you say when you say in to Madre that's not really like saying in your mother
In your shit
Oh, that's weird. We're there. They're there. No, no, no, it's not me and me and that is not the same thing
Yeah, that is not the same thing. It's just here's the thing psyche the culture in Mexico, right?
This is a Mexican slang, but I want to stick it in
I
Psyche
Psyche the Mexican culture in Mexican culture the most respected the most respected
family member in one's life is the mother
Yeah, no, no, no, it's the mother. It's the mother the Virgin Mary
Oh, it's the Virgin. It's the Virgin Mary. Okay
Say you're boring. Okay. Look 300 glow
The grandmother is the matriarch. That's yeah, you're right the grandmother's a matriarch
But what I'm saying is in Mexican culture, you're the saint and mother like the mother has a lot of respect
the mother has a lot of respect you know you did someone's mother it's like a
big deal then you come to America right and little shit has talked to their mom
like garbage like shut up bitch like ill like I went on a Ferrari like you take
the Lamborghini and like a young man like I hate you bitch that's been saying
right
Alright, and then you wonder why everyone wants to annihilate the US because they live it in that
Nobody wants to my life
Nope not one person you're going crazy
Yeah, I am I am going off the charts. I'm gonna send a well look. I'm not the one robbing a bank
It's on live fucking panic. It went from it went for mothers to you trying to annihilate the world
Not me not me and now you guys here's the discord link if you'd like to join me disorder
Okay, I'm speaking Spanish will wake us gets me
Yeah, hey, can I see your pinga or your uh, how do you what else do you say your pinga? You know what that means?
Hey, the chicken legs again chicken lifetime
Yeah, what do you see what I'm wearing? I'm getting wings chicken wings ain't no thing, but it's chicken wing
Look at that chicken
Guys also have the cash up going on the screen if you'd like a reading tonight
I will be happy to do a reading for you, but you know now that I'm not monetized
I'm happy to be a little like, you know, more of a dick about
All the free readings, but if you're on panel, I will give you a free reading
I'm starting to rub wickers wickers go back
Granite to make sure the mom means everything on earth to a family
Everyone join my disc
What are you saying? Hey NYPD. I love your mom
man, what's up, man, what's up,
Hold on. I'll see you hang out with your own palm bombers. That's the funniest thing on earth. It's like
Your own palm bombers, that's a new fucking, you know, that's new territory. Let me tell you
These two digs
Check it out. The ones that hate you and paul bomb you said that and now they got you by the balls
We a little wig on while they're here
Right sick white wickers how many times did you pull mom sack you piece of shit?
How many times you motherfucker keep chewing on your ugly Mexican face?
What do you do?
Bad.
Take no...
I never saw...
You don't have to...
This is what you do?
You don't have to chew a pen.
And you're bowing the corner.
So this is...
Listen, you're fucking...
This is what you do for fun.
This is stupid mask.
Yeah, take that...
Take that headphones off.
You're a shitty job, which obviously is being an N. I. P. D. Police officer, right?
You're over your back
I'm just asking you yourself
Alice is going too crazy, but if somebody didn't want to come because Alice was up here
We get a lady if you're going crazy. I know he's already going crazy. He's already he's already left building the bitch
well
Yes, he is
What's a Mexican sandwich called is it called a torta?
Yeah, yeah, okay. I'm the I'm the Brit. I'm the meat in your torta right now. Oh, yeah
Dumbly for you
Give me some tequila and
I'ma give you this meat. I'ma give you
You're in the middle
You go 23 that's a w w is a three but it's like 23
I'ma give you i'ma give you these carnitas while 300 glow gives you the lengua
Oh
Yeah
Yeah, I know Spanish sick. Don't you're not gonna fool me. I know Spanish. I'm talking about the meats. I'm not talking about the
Object, you know, you guys are wild it go. Okay. Do you want to look with it? Okay? Good. I'm wild man
This is one of the best shows on YouTube and it's like it was too hot for YouTube and now I'm back again
But I don't know if this one's gonna be too hot for you. It's out. Whoo. Oh, is that Mexican cookies?
Oh, bakery stuff. Oh my god. I see someone
Is that a talk that it's tough with cream like you like me. Oh, I like you stuff with cream. Oh, yeah
I want to be stuffed with 300 glow
Yeah, I thought them but lonely. No, no, I don't like that
Hot dogs are disgusting. Hey, rain come on up here. I'm gonna talk to some Mexican guys, you know, you know rain. She's uh
Beaners rain rain like rain posted a photo. She's like, this is what I think I look like in my flannel
It's like an LL bean flannel thing and then she's like this is what I look like and it was like a Cholita rain rain go away
Rain rain come here. I'm panel
W I like when it rains
Rain I like it when it rains come. I like it when it rains money
on my ass. I'm just kidding. I like it. I like it when psyche
doesn't look like a shit too. That's great. I like when I
look like Suzanne Summers. What are you talking about? I want
I want psyche to look. I want I want psyche to look like rain.
I know how I am. Oh, but you know, it's going to blow inside
of me all the way. I want to I want all 300 inches.
Ooh, oh, that's a margarita, right?
It's a limonita. Oh, just lemon soda. Okay, lemon soda.
Is that a lot of chili on that rim of it?
Ooh, look at you suck its tongue out at me.
Is that a little chilly on it? I don't like Mexican
I'm not entirely on my lemon someone was like doing a piece of candy and they're Mexican and they give me some candy and all
It's in my fault and chili. I was like, oh, what is this? And they're like, oh, this is Mexican candy
I'm like Mexicans eat this
Big nose loving this I could tell I don't I'm enjoying this
I'm not a great shit. Okay. I'm a do I look better without the wig turnig low. I'm cute, huh?
You have to say so yourself, you know, you know
Okay, yeah, thank you. Oh a lingua
baby taste of him I
Taste I taste like I taste like chicken
I'm just gonna take a sick of that my chasing
What do you got what do Mexicans do for Thanksgiving?
Do you like dress like Indians or what have origins with our cousins? Oh you do? Oh, man
How do you say cousin primos your primos?
Okay
nah, we um I
Well, I celebrate dancing even by myself mother's most of the time because I'm all grown up, you know
Well, you're supposed to go your family's house
I do I do like I go on the next day or the big day before or the if I have the day off
I go on the day of you know, yeah
My I'm my girl makes my turkey for show. I'm like make my turkey special for me
You do the turkey base there. Oh, oh
What do you mean what I look to the turkey base? Yeah, you base the turkey. Oh, yeah
We'll never forget take out the take out the innards of a turkey
The number leave in that bag because it's not very good if you leave that in sick for show. Yeah
Hey, 54 people in chat. Thank you guys for coming tonight. Wow. We're having a fun night. I love it
Well, we have any requests chat. You have to like let me know what's going on like rain. Are you to come up here?
What's he dressed like
New York
Okay, I found what does it say? Hold on it says
Burning joint USA. Oh, yeah, look at him. He's wearing a tie. I
Like it what it's on the tie. Oh, I'm wearing the wrong hat retard
It's the only one that looks good with this shit
Where the Dodgers had Nick
Me when you didn't see me on doing lot my channel were you worried and then you found me again?
How'd you find me? And I want to know
When told I had to stop you you stalk me. Oh, no, how about you?
I have a few that's how I want my viewers to come on. I've been stalking your ass. I'm like shit. Oh, yeah
That's right. I'll believe you. I've been stalking your ass. I'm just kidding. Okay, Casey says I'm lacking in self-awareness if you're gonna
Oh, it's okay. It's good to be lacking in self-awareness is
Absence of an ego and that's a good thing actually in spiritual
Want to be like watch my back. Well, I don't know you're watching it to that
I don't feel like that
Used to when people were but no well now. I feel like it now because there's 50 people watching me actually 52
Yes
What I am I'm not impressed and the results because I know you could do it what I am
point out is
That you know what I mean these sorts of things it's sort of like and it's like in the markets like an economy, okay?
You'll give the economy you you supply the demand
What do people want though I'm trying to figure out what do you guys?
Showing the people what they want so they
Getting the benefits
That's right and more
I want to see you just find
just hook people up with uh
I mean I don't know about this neck guy
this neck guy like arrived
like about like two minutes ago
but yeah you know what man
this is my first time on the show
ever
it's the first time on this channel probably
as I am for the last like maybe two hours, but yeah sure everybody scan that QR code Jones like he's just like he's yeah
Yeah, yeah during the cold. I'm gonna see 300 gloves
Body shape gonna go like his discord. Yeah
There we go. Hell, yeah
I'm gonna do a chatter with Chris K this year. I'm looking for more collabs though. I need to do some collabs
So any takers don't worry just be consistent psyche. Don't do too much math. It'd be good. Okay. Well, that's a great
Okay
Well, thank you. Yeah, I came exactly like
It's like a cold jolly rancher
Well, don't worry about oh and it's done. Don't worry about these people. All right, you know what I mean, yeah
Yeah, I
Where's Alexander mayors cuz I'm just trying to pipe think of smoking out of a plastic pipe w
She's good. I'm just trying to pipe
Alexander and I have the same birthday. That's crazy
So I will fall just cut you there. Yeah shout out to the
Folders
What's up whore fixing my website?
Gatorade
With the wig on or off
When I'm eating fat ass nigga keep drinking your coolie
And Gatorade
stupid ass and I keep drinking
I'm a fucking drinkin yellow fucking lemonade ass stupid ass
And you can't even form a sentence here
Can't even shut the fuck up and suck my dick here
My dick, you know, I mean I got my penis like blacks
Cool. You got a penis. I'm pretty sure everybody up here has a penis. So what's your point? I got a penis. I don't have
Last nigga
You ain't got no weenus
My real name is be like this bitch
Like 12 that's like you fucking cap 300 you cap in here
No, no, I'm good. No, no, no, no, no, no, I'm good. You want to see a back stage right now. No, I'm good brother. Thanks
You scared you scared to see some big
Yeah, you'd be all scared of seeing my shit wiggling on your face and shit pussy ass
What a weird thing to say
Shit pussy ass
About it
How's that a W?
You're all scared and shit about it facts
Set there and
What am I scared of
You know
Why are you even a love back on this? Why are you love back up here your camera on bro, shut up?
Signal could you change your name could you change your name by the way?
I know exactly who the fuck you are you're not gonna tell me what to do
Would you like me to tell you to shut up this nigga's got a little ass dick, bro
This nigga's all scared and shit
That was very rude. You know, I don't know him
That was very mean of you to say that you shouldn't miss out. That's
you
Can you say start out to use that you're
Sorry, I'm sorry big you're all miserable and shit
About you bro
Shout out to you, bro. I hope you see better days one boy
You're one of the reason why I came up with the word dumb dumb literally I remember you
Yeah, I'm going to take a big shot for you. My boy. I hope you see better days, bro.
Honestly, I hope you see better days, bro. And I hope you shut the fuck up.
We all hope you know something. Cheers to you, my boy. Cheers to you, my boy.
Stop saying cheers and take your shot. I'm asking.
All right, fuck you then
You can't peer pressure me to take a shot when you're being a bitch you shut up you ain't taking the shot
You're not gonna peer pressure me bro. I'm gonna take a shot with my boy 300 glow
I'm
See brah
Wrong that's a fucked up. Oh
I'm finna. Oh, you guys are pushing it. And by the way, I have honest question
Why is this you love that job on your panel?
That's my girlfriend 300 glow. He won't come up. Oh you behave yourself. We I mean, can you be forgiven for what you've done, sir?
I don't know. I
Share pages up on the stream W
What's that? Hey, this shit just got interesting
I just got a really horny
Oh man, I just missed a shot with you guys bro
I was trying to cheers with you guys
Let me know what it's
Let's do one now
I'll do one with you brother
No, no, you'll do one with me
Alright, pull
Alright, let me pull him
Let me pull my puppy
Until pages on something like since I joined some kind of weird
Right. Cheers big dearest
No, she turned her camera off because I was I said I was gonna goon because she was there
But when you say shit like that, you're not like we actually believe
Because you're a weird motherfucker fine. Okay, you know, you're a weird motherfucker. You accept it
Okay
So cool the mind would you?
I don't really care so what if I'm jacking off the prairie page so why
Who cares if you did I care motherfucker. You said he cares I'm here
That I'm doing it. Yo, did you have a bad day or something, bro?
And you know that yes
You don't realize that
Yesterday this is the first time you've ever dealt with something you don't like
Well, I've dealt with you. Well, that's a dumb ass bus. You
Get to pick you get to kick somebody off if you want to okay, you get that privilege
There's your choice
Give me the power because I don't know you you're the only female up on panel
about a bunch of and the holy choice
Hear me out it doesn't really matter who I kick and who's replaced it's probably still going to be the same atmosphere
Thing like saying all of a sudden you only hear this droning
I
How was that man?
How is this the house time? We don't kick anybody and we just
What we were doing
Hey, no, fuck that we're taking somebody
I'm taking myself fuck it at this point you thank you
Who just said thank you just adapt just adapt
Wow
We have
You say father chicken leg father chicken leg yes, exactly
Can you leave the fucking cat alone
Can you shut the fuck up and stop
of all that was you know what he's like
you know what he's like
If you actually want to know what my goal is, you're a fucking retard.
You shouldn't be on the film.
I'll give you four and four and how many times I don't like you.
You know that.
Thank you.
I'm sad.
Guys, we're taking a new leaf on this show.
We're all going to get along like friends.
All right.
Yes.
No, we're not going to get along with this guy.
Yeah
Yeah guys wow guys that was my life guys we're having so much fun
This is like old times. It really is because it's like remember how wild it used to be
But you don't ruin it by kicking people out. Yeah
Come back in the panel we need to see
I like nice seeing guys. All right. All right. All right, Mr. Bean
Everyone cover the little cat knows this because the stage is coming up to smoke out the whole house
No, I ain't no cent, but that is a nice fucking hat she's wearing.
God, it's okay.
Man, look at my skin.
We're liquorheads.
I will but now we have a message we have a special message from the
A cult of cocks up, if I like it.
Garden of broken gods, we plant our screens like seeds,
out of pixels, prayer girls.
We call it a cult, but it's really a communion
between the wound and the one who tends it.
You're gathered in the glow of screens,
our rosaries made of emojis, our hymns, corrupted files,
yet still we rise singing through distortion.
The cult of psyche burns in the bandwidth.
There we go. Thank you Lenore for filming that that was a beautiful W
Beautiful beautiful little video
Yes, just whoever did that video you guys put in there was that's not a special guest
Hey, let me see do I have another
I have, uh, well, I have, like, I have a library.
That makes a mass terrorist in, uh, square two, just took a shot, so, cheers.
Every, every crewman video, what's this?
My little mass terrorist friend.
Are you tired of reality not glitching in there?
Do you crave deeper thoughts, but also snakes?
Welcome to the Cult of Psyche.
Still not convinced?
Apply telepathically or just follow us
too long you know you should have sort you should sort that up it's too long
four seconds shorter that would be good
that would be good
i'm not hating that
i like it
that's what your mom said sir
oh
i don't see smoke page i don't see the house burning down
Did some answers came up?
Firefighters like out the window what happened to the sage burn out. Oh my god
Beautiful hair beautiful eyes beautiful now
Can I tell her if you don't mind
Are you too? Are you playing
operation? Why do you have the
tweezers? Because they're tiny.
I'm thinking to get wet and I
have to not. Oh, she's starting
to find your dick here.
I'm going to remain in now.
No sage cleaning. Thanks.
That's all you have to say. No
cleaning. You're remaining now
with wickers, 300 glow
and some
fat asshole named crucible
ghost.
Yeah, it's not bad as call me by the right name. It's so we tell you
You are 300 chubs
They're ostrich legs. I'm big so we tell you
Hey, get that shit straight put them there before
Yeah, next up 300 glow the fucking dirty ceiling all right
We're gonna have to paint that ceiling and the one to the cabin. Yeah looks a little crazy
You know, I don't start thinking about this, you know, but by the time I get done with you, you're going to have a new kitchen, brother.
All right, so it's like on the other side.
Oh, fuck, here we go.
But I don't go with the pina colada, because it's renovation time.
You're?
Yeah, I think.
I think the wrong filter would be crazy.
Look how weak is the chia pet.
Just
You got to understand what's happening do you
What's up?
Hey, that's rude.
Yeah, I know I'm here, baby, but I know where I am.
And you understand, but they don't think you've been here.
They think he's coming back in two seconds.
He's not.
He left you here alone to help yourself.
I guess you mean you little f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f
Yeah
Not what you're an advocate for Mexican losers. Look at what?
Look at these two bad losers here again shine. Yeah
You're crazy 300 glow walks around in a kick dirty kitchen
All day, they all putting up gang sons for the past two hours. I send this loser now leave our kitchen
Little Mexican faggots. I own both you cheer pet motherfuckers little Mickey Mouse niggas
Yo, you put your cabinet you you put your cabinet door because of me motherfucker
You didn't have cabinet doors until I said something and say has the same dirty fucking construction jacket on his dirty chair
For two years straight you have mental
Quacky hands in the phone
You have met the problem for me
Take that mask off and go look in the mirror and say yo, I'm one crazy motherfucker
I'm the biggest loser that ever existed. This is what I do with my life
Mascot and
Like I'm a chia pen fat Mexican and I'm a loser two losers
One's in the kitchen one thing to talk and one thing to get in one thing to chair
You know which time you spend that
Tom down you're yelling shut the fuck up. You can talk quietly dude. Turn your fucking life down. It's not
God damn bro
That's what you guys be on
So
Yo, NYPD your boys told you to shut the fuck up
Well, at least turn the fucking mic down a little bit god damn
I'm yelling
What's up, man? Here's ladies
Take another shot. Eat some more. You're good.
You were saving your life.
I was just going to keep crying.
W to him. Let a real man drink.
You just say W to everything.
What is when somebody might say W
and he's crying about it, murdering your brother into W.
You're going to die tomorrow, bitch.
Are you going to be that tomorrow, nigga?
You ain't going to have to double you.
You ain't gonna hold
Www drink and then eat some more and shut the fuck up
Don't worry about my goals my boy. I don't give a fuck about your goals. My boy
Worry about my cause don't worry about where I'm going
You can't even drink look at these two freaks
Like how do I like your last girl's name was bad
It's about that time for a night night
That time for a night not sir
Really ain't never give me no chance. Oh, we don't know. I mean we don't know what you're talking about
Would you like to go nightmares?
You don't know what I'm talking about
You don't even know what the fuck you're talking about.
What's the last thing you just said?
What was the last thing you just said?
You're just going to keep repeating it.
Same-ass questions.
You can't go out.
I'm a retard in shit, but you all niggas keep all bitchin' in shit.
Yeah, what do you mean by bitchin do you mean that like what do you mean that by like what do you mean by bitchin?
there you go you're good you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you
of the
the
Show me the bow for I didn't make it clean if I did make it clean the burden the fruit would be on me
But I didn't make it clean. Well, I didn't make it come I said sick was a fucking dumbass and I can prove it
You win dammit. Oh
Man now now prairie page is gonna come back. That's a well not with you. You're being weird
Shut up man fucking you're weird
Shut up you stop talking like that you're it
By the way, the bottom of it does say the people's pocket
What you wouldn't like to I'll give you to the non-being thankful
I'm being gracious. I'm being, you know, awesome.
Oh, Johnny, stop it. Look at her acting on this.
Check the score, Gary.
Oh, Johnny's the monster. Don't, ha-ha.
You gave me that Johnny fucking laugh.
He-ha-ha-ha. You monster psychopathic lunatic.
Stop trying to pull on psyches fucking the psychological string and shit like a pretty girl psyche. Oh take my rent shut up
You're the craziest bitch up here, Johnny
Yeah, leave Johnny alone you mean weird you always be weird
Like a little like a little kid in tonight. She's pretty. Hey, it's singing 300 glow. Thanks for being on the show
It was it was fun. It was like you got a little too wild
We'll come back later when you calm down a little bit. We're trying to have some
I'd make the argument against that. I would never have stick Beckham of your show if it was me, but you know you do
Hey, Zachary
But I like, I like the ring of glow and we have Nick Johnson here. Exactly
Yeah, we have a lot of people up here now. I mean, I mean, I just want to say
The site was glow, glow wasn't even, it was a glow, do you know, you say something? I don't know
There's something
Yeah, he just made it around SIG though, he won't throw this
All right, Joanie, I'll, okay, everyone else can come up
Are you so good?
Love you guys. I love when the fuck you get them. I love you too. Oh, it's dumb ass. Love you too. Dumb dumb
Yeah, we're having a we're having a
Hey, when's you get a black cat?
This Lenore is my back. This is my kitty Lenore. That's that who he thinks
This is my cat. I thought you had a fucking
When did you get that? Do you always have that? Oh, that's you. That's a cute fucking cat
She's very cute. My little babe, Eleanor.
I need you to add a couple cats.
I don't think I've ever seen.
I may be asking. I actually don't know, but...
Well, here's Eleanor.
And who else do I have around here?
Well, Rudy's around here.
Rudy's sleeping right there,
and Trix is sleeping right behind me.
Can you see Trix here?
I'm just gonna have to get her.
She's a little bit of a bitch, isn't she?
Um Lenore. No, she's just like the she's like a little black. No
Tricks or whatever the other one or tricks tricks a little boy. Yeah. Yeah, he's like, um, he's just uh,
He's very very sweet actually. He's very sweet. Yeah, we have a pretty much to jump on you
I should jump on the desk and show
Hi page. Sorry
What's up now?
I was having fun. I was gonna be I was gonna defend page actually
Hi. What's up? Who's screen picture is that burning joint? I like that little picture.
That is Nick Johnson. I know. I like your picture, buddy. It's
super cool. Yeah, we found a bunch of fruit. Are you kissing me? I'm going to try to see
When when they smoked it and remember the high
The scary movie the parody like they made fun of like wait no what is the cause
Very movie. I think it's called like pretty sure it's called scary movie. It is called scary movie. Yeah, okay, okay
Scary movie one of the scary movies that were made in that decade
You guys hear that they're bringing that back the weight weight weight Williams brothers. They're bringing it back
They're gonna make another parody like
They had to wait this like what it's been like fucking like 15 year whatever they're gonna
We're gonna make another parody movie out and I guarantee it's gonna be awesome
Well, my favorite I do have a favorite scene from that movie
I'm just afraid to show it right now because there's a hilarious
But we'll just say it
Well, Charlie Sheen goes
He's walking he hears this like singing voice and he's you know, Charlie Sheen is in one of the screen movies
He goes and he's like he sees his daughter like playing with
wrapped in a shroud and he's like
and she started saying weird things
hello get under the blanket with me daddy
and then he's like
who are you
I'm your daughter
it's like no you're not and he pulls the sheet
and it's Michael Jackson
yeah
yeah I know exactly what you're talking about
so Michael
fucking jumps out the window
oh look at the kitchen
here she is now
I
Somebody has to tell what the fuck it's there in it. Yeah, you want to debate yet?
You will debate. Yeah, where does she see you? Hey master debate you want to debate here?
Let me run one with the cat put the cat on the mic if you don't mind
Burr yeah, like a burr in your fur or a tinky tinky like a bully
Hey, don't be staring at me you're what you want to roam on here
Let me run with the cat
What are you doing bury buns?
It's because you call him that name
You're kind of like bird like for icebergs up in the fur
And the funny story about him is actually when we got him he was super tiny and I didn't we didn't know if he was a girl
Or a boy. I thought he was a girl so I need to ember and then he came to burr
By the time I found out he was a boy because his nuts came late and
I just I can hear him. I can hear it purring in the fucking microphone
Hey, yeah
But you want to be a you want to be a ghost cat here
Hey, I'll adopt you here
I can hear it purring
He's a happy guy. He's just a happy bully. That's cuz he's talking to the ghost though
Yeah, all right, I'll but I won't debate to me. I won't debate the cat. I'll let him off. I'll let you off on
You know, but next time next time you jump up here curtain in the mic, brother, you're gonna get it
His eyes are glowing it looks fucking scary
Yeah, you in the nighttime in the dark freedom look at him. Oh my gosh on my I just turn it on my TV to see if it made a
Difference like I could read the chat better too
Fucking looks crazy cats are fucking cats and predators man. There's like little ass cats. It's like dogs
But it's not really like dogs though cats are just like little fucking like some big cats like lions and shit like there's a little
Yeah, but you ever seem like a wild fucking cat. They're fucking voracious. They're hunters like so fucked up
Yeah, they're pretty unforgiving. They're just worthless. They just they're but a dog we domesticated them so much. I mean
It's not like a look or nothing
So crucible get ready for a reading and I want to see her
Because last time she cheated me and I got the butterfly and she was
You're right. Yeah, so she cheated me and I need a reading page. First of all, I apologize to Alice for doing that
And I want you to close it
It was the courage you got the butterfly
You got the nightingale dick, you know, I got the white
the nightingale
Remember, I mean, I am the night
No, the nightingale
It sounds like
One with two heads whatever she just didn't do it on time. She played us. I'm not behind that
That's the fuck up you guys or I'm not doing it again
What the hell is a nightingale?
What the fuck is a nightingale?
Is that a bird?
What the hell is it?
Motherfucker, what does the butterfly mean?
Because I guess it means you.
Baby, I want to see shelfling in my face and the tiger better fly out if I get the butterfly
Better be a fucking Leo. Yeah
No, better be on live camera. I'm not taking a word for it. Oh
You you else
I
Don't want to do a reading but I will I was doing something else. I'm gonna mute because it's loud
Yeah, we don't want you to we want to hear it though. That's the whole point of it. Like it's we like it
The show thinks you're cool, right? They want to hear that we want to hear that. It's awful. Yeah
Damn picture my camera
Imagine the way she shuffles imagine what she can do with you no god didn't think oh, yeah
You got you out by the way, she fucked you up. There's no
Now give him the butterfly
But last time it was the blind and she's like you got the butterfly. I'm like, did I or are you just fucking with me?
Cuz someone had a good lap page. Can you please give Alice a reading if you don't mind if it's
That randomly is that?
Okay, you tell me that I love I didn't fuck it up
You gotta say when dumbass
Holy shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes shes
So that's actually the most beautiful cards are just not masculine.
Like you want to be okay.
It's okay.
You can put a fly in the mouth.
I downgrade.
What the fuck, bro?
And that wasn't even planned.
So that's scary, bro.
See what I'm saying?
I'm gonna throw up.
Alright ghost you're next
We have a good time page can you please do me? Can you please give me one?
Yeah
The moth the moth it all right
Impulsive he's deep and wishful. Ah, here it is the moth is
Around the other side moth energy that play when we're attracted to easy solutions or anything shiny and new
Yeah, I was trying to email.
Disappointment or burnout.
It's helpful to remind mob personalities that life is complex, no matter the illusion.
No one is exactly...
from the child.
What is that?
Anyways, no one is exempt from the trials and tribulations of this great journey practice seeing life as an infinite mystery rather than wishing it was easy or different
When in balance enthusiastic and whimsical when out of balance ideal I or idolizes others
Jittery and to bring into balance start finishing some projects
That's what I call the more
Sounds like a bitch me
Yeah, the more
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Ah signals here hit him up. Let's see. What's it? Yeah, well, I don't know why he's here
I don't know why you'd buy him back up. Whatever. I'm like
Back up big psyche. Obviously let him back off
Let both be fixed back up
Appreciate her. You're trying to keep you up. I get a reading. Could I get a reading?
Yo, let me do me
Your stuff away. You're gonna have to go. I want 300 shuffles
Oh, God, you have both of them back up. This is why you go through first. I want 300 shuffles. That's just gonna be a
Hey, she's doing cards. I like in this I can see the witch aura coming off of her
I don't know that's your cards
You expect you expect me not to say anything I just got a second
Your about which?
You don't know that
Okay
While she's doing the readings and then wait your turn, okay, okay ghost because your second this is for you, right?
Yep, tell me tell me when when you would you like me to stop?
When top or middle I'm gonna have to go middle
That
This is one of my favorite page
Pardon me
Every time you
Listen butterfly you're talking to a bat right now be quiet. Let her read it
We'll talk in a minute Alex shish for now, please. Okay, the bat darkness and letting go death we leading to rebirth
So again another transformation card. We did just have
Cycle so that makes sense. Well, so be
That awaits for the Sun to set in the moon to rise in the darkness
It can see all that was invisible in the daylight hours
The bat is a master of the subtle senses for the underlying forces that cause some things to prosper and others to fade
The back card shows up to signify the ending of a chapter, the closing of a door.
The back comes swiftly encouraging us to move on in just a few hours and new day dawns.
No more lingering in the past.
One in balance accepts, adapts, and adjusts.
One out of balance refuses to let go and reminisces.
To bring into balance, watch some more sunrises, ghost.
I have a question for you. Does it say that the back crunches out?
Well, I mean a back could crush but they can't really they
There's stability, right
Lace them out a fucking bug
Better the more for the back the more three
Nope the bad eats ma the bad
Most of us all right, so what's next?
I think 300 asked first.
Correct.
is there a dumb dumb card or no no stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop bottom or go
you got to answer the question grab the the bottom third of it the quarter of it
Well, that's a new that's a new
Literally three answers
That's new technology that's uncharted waters. He got the dolphin
Probably probably because he's gay who else will get the dog. Yeah, that's just one of our
All right, no one's ever gotten the beaver book. Oh, yeah, they have never mind
Where the fuck is it? Oh, there we go. Okay. I got the
Ever if I was on my channel, it might be a little bit different, but even then I'm so myself
So this is who I am. Yes, she's freestyling. She's freestyling. Wait up. I'll be all me myself
a healer light and blessings
She's reading a book. She's never the peacetime. She's reading a book, but
Okay, let's do another talk because i'll go start out
But come and see my channel. I do do not need the cards. I can't stop being rude to us
Yeah, okay, so the dolphin is about like it's a subtle energy. It's comes with healing and it comes with light and it comes with
Ideas and creativity. It's about like
Don't like don't underestimate you
You know because you can always make a big impact and don't underestimate yourself either and I feel like anyone that comes into karma or into
contact with a personality
it like is like the wheel of karma so if you know anything about tarot like that's the wheel
of fortune it's like no matter what is it's fated it will be like you can make your free will
choices you can do what you want but no matter what that's still going to be the outcome it's
like you have a greater pull on and control on yourself your atmosphere your environment your
whole life and I think that you know you can make good things happen for other people too so this
card is also an indicator of profound blessings on the way so you kind of just come with luck like
and or maybe like a dubby part of me
i'm a walking dubby yeah okay well that makes a lot of sense you know it's because
i think that and people who run into you it like you can change the entire course of their life
You're just a beacon for W. Who's I guess if that's what you want to call is that I have a question page
Is that like the yin and yang like that dolphin card? Can is it kind of like?
Like negative and positive if you get one of them
Her phone died my energy is that crazy
Damn
You should have said you're swimming w not a walking w. I mean I would have laughed at that
Yeah
No, what's up boy
Her shit cut off while reading my energy
Hating on me right now
So much fucking power
As a bat I use my energy my echolocation to cut that shit off here
You don't get a ring sir
My love
Hey special guest I give you want your sample over that shit
Do a flip jump over. What do you want to put jump?
Give $70 to
If you do a front a front flip I guarantee I'll send it you guys know me I guarantee I'll send it
Matter of fact, if you actually make a front flip, I'll go I'll get psyche $200 years and psyche knows I'm telling the truth
From flip over that shit Johnson's gonna burn his boozle
No, I suppose that motherfucker. You got a flip
Busted my ass
They give us that I see man. I see that brother. It's okay
Soccer man in a sec. I'll make it easier for you backflip over it was that Kansas soccer goal right here
I didn't take into consideration. Oh
No, I don't want to reach on jump over fire. I want to fuck with yours
Yeah, everybody still didn't fall in the fire
Matter of fact, if you throw a flip over, if you literally do a flip, if you make it, I'll get like $300 right now.
It's like, you know, and Alex, he tells all the shit he wants, but he knows I'll fucking, I got some money, $300 if you fucking flip over.
That fire is such a little pussy.
Never mind, never mind, I take it back, you might actually try.
I jumped over, I think.
You're gonna get hurt.
Nah, I'm done, you're gonna get hurt.
Nice try, man.
Do a flip, dum-dum.
You know
If you shut down
And that's you not be a retard
I'll give $300 right now. Yeah, no because the hospital is gonna be
Actually, I feel ashamed of myself for even asking you to do that because you're probably retarded. You probably would do it.
I don't know. I'm trying to be better though. I'm trying.
Do I have permission to cash out? Yo, what's up having it doors?
You have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you
Motherfucking dog being
Your motherfucking dolphin
I'm a motherfucking dog. You she said she said it bro that way you're swimming in because you're swimming in dick you heard
I'm swimming in that bitch. Shut the fuck up. You're talking to a bat you heard
No, I'm thorned in your
I
Don't be jealous don't be jealous
don't be jelly
peanut butter jelly
I actually have jelly
ooh let's dig it
we actually recorded it as well
I actually have baby
w
Don't be jelly. Oh, the jelly. Oh
Now I did he came from sick sick as W. What do you guys say that W? What do you guys say that?
I'm on you you dumb dumb
Look how much
Look how many donations I got already and look how much money as like you really want to
Would you really want to go?
That's the one you really want to do it. You ain't get donations like me
No, I I'm actually the person that like spans the money
like
You don't get
I'm done entertaining you bro. I made that bitch the power turn off in her house. I'm a W
I hope you guys have a good night. Okay, man. Do you another self-retard?
And you shouldn't be a lot back up here you ran like a bitch
It's really too long. I literally I I literally spend more in a week
You look at all the channels that I fucking donate you I spend more in a week that you make like
And I'm not even an act buddy with the money shit. Oh
Trashing now. We don't tell me I'm crashing the fuck out. I got permission. I
Literally spend more than you make I literally spend more than you make
I know we all know what you mean relax. What do you mean relax? Okay? I can talk it if I spend more than you make
Why?
Make my money. Why are you mad at me for it?
He's putting his toes in the fire. I don't give a fuck about his toes in the fire
why you bet me for every page? Oh, no. Oh
You want to make an argument? Okay? No, that's a win again. Do I do I not my channel for a reading sir
I don't give a funny. Yeah, but uh, do I not spend more do I not spend more than you make?
I mean, let's make whatever you never do native or per page for reading
And you milk her for free readings up here like I'm next. I'm next
Well, it depends what you mean by three
You've been
Donate
thousands and not a pen is a page
You know, that's because I'm such a nice guy. She ain't she likes it
She likes to talk that dumb ass shit and I'm respectful. So I just let her talk. Well, she's listening ansel
What I know she's listening. I know it's like, you know, who else is that you got the nightingale card the other night
That's what Europe said. I
Literally spend more in two days and you making a like fucking month
Like easily, so why can't you donate to a page if you make that much?
She don't have a channel. She's not monetized don't fuck
Okay
She might have a cash up. She's not here's the argument. She's not monetized. She doesn't have a user channel dumb dumb
Are we really that retarded?
We are
It's a white circle
Go to go to the picture hit the picture then you go to edit avatar and then you
You pick another picture and click back your your YT or whatever TY shit, and it'll bring it back on
All right, so be a loser with white with a nipple hang around
Yeah, I'm ghost I don't give a fuck
Yes, sir
Well, the point was because you can
Listen
I thought I made the claim the bird
Okay, I'll make your argument for you by the way, I know the most was you know, well, I do actually make more than you
I
Don't I don't go down from the butterfly to the more all right page
You're a mom you're a butterfly you might you know butterflies a little bit better, but you're a mom
I didn't give you the car brother. What's it mean?
Shut up dickhead. I know but just shut up. Anyway, I didn't say
Cheer pat loser in the corner or the porn bomber the faggot
I
He's fucking knocked out
Why would you ever let him
Yeah, why why
Look at Nick Johnson careful Nick, you're gonna burn the tie, bro. It also black
Now I'm done. I'm done crashing out. Are you second to going back up?
I pray to God that page is talking to you, but it does hurt. You think what she's saying? What's you say?
What's you say? Well, I'm gonna read it to you dick. It does
Shit don't cause oh shit. That means you think who I am a shit yard
So page you said you think you've never done it
And that's why you don't don't they they make fun of her readings because you don't believe in her readings
You know what for the first time in my life. No
Your mark
Let me talk if you let me talk for the first time ever and goes in my whole life
I will apologize the page. I did not mean to do that
I'm sorry
This is your mother clipping ship is the first time I'm ever gonna say sorry and that shouldn't mean it
I'm sorry, David. I did not mean that
I'm sorry if you took it that way. I have options
You clip it and ship it boys
Here
Okay, can you please come back up here? I I already said I apologize don't beat me up about it here
Well, that's you you're making sure you're not just engaged at least join and talk about it
I'm not gonna try to debate you. I promise I swear to God. I'm not gonna try to do this
Your mic sounds like shit
Don't burn up all the floor
No, she's working on Canadian time, you know that works
By the way, what is human though, and what is all scarily
Will come text like a wicked
Would you like me would you like me to call him what do you want me to call him for what do we do?
I
Do I have permission to crash out how was your ghost over Alex
Besides getting hooked up by me how's your just over
Pretty good not too bad and guess what's gonna happen that's thanks ghostie
Instead of Thanksgiving, we stay night heat going, yeah?
By the way, you talk shit, you talk all night shit, but you may pay for it.
No shit.
Yeah!
Fucking go, yeah?
Wow, this is good
That's how you know, the haunts are like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like
Do whatever you think you can do.
I'll show you.
I'm gonna make him kick the ass out.
Yay!
Stop!
It's very loud.
Psych is proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud
Get out of your way, GERD!
Do I ever make you do that?
Yeah!
Fucking go!
Good!
What you making-
The dream, don't be dumb to the ones who doubt
He's the reason the flame never went out
So raise your glass, the ghost are out
It's ghost don't...
Oh, it's not sticking on the shot, brother
Oh, it's...
Sticking on the shot
God damn, that's a beautiful song
Can I say you heard this you guys don't mind
Let's fucking go let's run one
Dum-dums
Beautiful song
You don't want to run one and pay just
Coming up
That's my
Can I apologize? Can I stop fighting? Can I apologize? I say nothing. Big guss is what the fuck he wants
My song is a lot better than yours. Hey, no arguing over songs
Yes, you can have a vote man, I used to be able to do polls in the chat
I think
You should treat with a little bit more respect like
And page you should submit a little bit more respect
Santa thank you. I'm trying to put you on a t-shirt. You talking what's your point?
I love you you dickhead. I love you too, but I'm trying to put you on a concert here. Yeah
Yeah, I remember played she was this way I'm talking you look that you heard
I'm just
Can we all this can't we all just get along? No, apparently not
Come on guys, you know what?
Your problem you like to send and you're something for big girls. I don't listen ma'am. I don't want you, okay?
Listen ma'am. Stop sin. Stop sending ma'am. Fine. I'll stop simping. Fuck
Okay, that's pretty good. People sent for page pages. It's up for anybody. No, they're thinking for ghost
Well, maybe you're probably paying to kick me off and shit, you know
Ghost you better behave okay, what are you?
You're being fucking I do drunk and belligerent he's being really cool and hanging out and just like
What's your actual problem
What am I doing to be rude to page I mean, it's like
Go ahead and name that shit. How was I rude? How am I being rude right now?
Because you know I'll fuck you up psych, right? Go ahead. You know I'll fuck you up. How was I rude?
And how am I being rude to her? Go ahead.
I'm gonna shove you cock in that.
You know you're not gonna, you know you're not, shut up Alex. When we run it was like,
you know you're not gonna put that fuck you up.
Okay, cool. You've already lost, but how am I being rude? Go ahead.
You see name is like you want to call me on your own panel and I'm sights boy
And I get caught up in everybody else's panel for being your fucking your boy. It's like you're gonna call me out
Let's run one. How am I being rude? Go ahead go ahead
Set the fuck up I'm talking the size you don't ask
She's got a kitty in her lap. You're gonna step there. You're shut the fuck up. You probably should just like call me
When you lose your argument, you're gonna play a song
This is why
for you
Alexander's heart's gone all the way
Smiling those prairie days. Yeah, she's a sweet heart
That's my Canadian badass my prairie page
I pray we play
From the Rockies to the lakes her laughter fly
And she can fucking retard you
Fucking retarded
And I'll tell you that
And she's hot.
She's hot.
Time to set the part off.
We're forever homin'
Prairie Pays
Me I make us
No, you may not go see well, I'm gonna make it
No, you have a little bit too much to drink you tonight
What's your argument I could I mean, what does it matter?
You love me because you I'm not just me ask you know that obviously you know that all right, what's your
to stop playing A.I. song, to stop starting B.
Stop being a fucking...
You're like, fucking do that.
It's a good song
Insulting me and the guests we're just trying to have fun and you're ruining the whole night by like being belligerent and annoying
Just like hang out and chill. Jesus Krimany
So I'll have fun. We I mean, it's like supposed to be fun. Not like
When we paid the fucking gold song, it was fun, right?
You just love it. This is the best nice. It's not playing there. Well, listen, I am the best
I'm better than you and you know
It's okay. How am I not better? How are you better than you?
Okay
Okay, all right
The permission to hang out and get along
That was good
You know Sanders being a gentleman tonight, so let's have everyone have fun six here
He's also a fucking dumbass
Like I mean
Well listen, but let me make the argument though. He sells crack
Half the days and half the days like you did
I don't leave it alone. It's your panel brother. I'm here to read. I'm here to
Have fun hang out. Okay
Have fun
I love you. Come on. Let's all have fun one have fun
Can I say this word?
Only if it's against me
No, that's not fun. Yeah already he once I was right
Want her to do that
If she don't know how to God, she's never got in her life.
She's not the fucking fucking God.
out of hand
I don't know why the fuck you're talking to me like that.
There's all you bunch of retards who want to join on one channel and fucking like talk to me like I'm the retard.
I think I should just end because it's like we're not getting anywhere.
I don't think you should. I think you should be going to go out if you're just going to go out with your arm.
Calm down. Calm down.
What the fuck
The show you literally let people back off that
It's just you're writing over I love Alexander over and over I think
No, I'm working on some characters for calendar. Oh nice
With Wade
They're gonna make a
Queens of YouTube calendar with all the girls on YouTube beat-up page
How cool
They just made it look like I'm crazy with that site and help them with you're like you're awesome
Oh, yeah, you know AI nests
They got the summer's photographer that takes the pictures of her like you know on those pictures
It's gonna do it, but they're all on board
Did you know?
The Queens of YouTube and each girl's a month
Even beat is on board
And then we're gonna do the guys
Gonna be ghost is January for the sake of you February. I'll be fucking you know the guys
Calendar that should have so at least a couple hundred grand hundred percent
Look at page I love Alexander over and on I'm not doing
Well, I mean nobody can really love a mosquito, right?
No one can love a mosquito is that what you just said?
Yep
That's what I will give you. Yep
Yeah, I
Like but you can love a Leo. You can love a little ahead always
Big guns
Always gives me good night. You want a little kiss you good night? I'll give you
What used to be for my fucking now show some feet you're it no
Can I get some ankle no
How much
Bunch of fucking retards run. Oh, you're drunk. No, this fucking retards run
You did have a little too much to drink didn't you tonight ghosties?
Yeah, I'm having to get done
If I have a bunch of flag will make target me against me though. There's a bunch of retards
Would you agree Alice you you're one of them by the way
I agree. It's retail city. I agree. I agree and I'll let it go my bed
Well, I'm not what makes me
No, you look fine. Oh and Paige is number one retard
Well, the psych looks like he's deep in his own God. I can trade it on something. He's doing this. No
I am cycle the pulse beneath your doubt the spark that survives every trial walk my path of college question boldly feel deeply
Rise after every fall
You are not servants but seekers. Carry my light into your shadows and shape your own ascent.
Sorry.
I'm doing cool things.
This is Alexander McQueen
You think after 20 years on these streets, I'd get used to the quiet
But it's the quiet that gets loud the paperwork the coffee cone cold the reflection in the glass
That guy looks like he used to laugh more
We just don't let it leak you learn to carry. Yeah, what's laughing? I haven't laughed in 20 years, baby
You think after 20 years on these streets, okay, so I mean stop it stop it stop Alexander stop
Sorry. Okay. Okay. Now I'm going to create the video. Okay. Yeah, I'm just doing some fun things, but I don't know why you can hear it all. Okay. I'm sorry. So sorry. Okay.
The same room as you via volume or like audio, I guess?
I know. I know. There's not that button on this one. Okay. Why isn't anybody in the chat talking? I'm getting suspicious that there's like 40 lurkers. That's kind of weird.
Come on guys. Can we participate in the chat? Can chat say something?
Why is it all being quiet? I feel like I'm being stared at hold on
We'll just ask a question and the but the ones that are that is me 40 people are here, but no one's shining
How many oh wait, I just threw that sorry. Sorry if it was loud. So what about
It's like you you should remember this one too because it's been a common trivia question is like what is the flock of flamingo?
It's called anyone who's been here before
I go a gag below
No, then boyance. Yes, it's a fun boy
Do you know what a
It's a bunch of
You know that
A group of giraffes. Yeah
Bunch of Tom other fuckers. I don't know
psyche and his boys
group of giraffes is called a
tower
And other terms are heard, journey, or a kaleidoscope of giraffes.
Oh, I like that a lot.
A kaleidoscope of giraffes.
What is a group of grillers called?
Wait, we're playing trivia all of a sudden. Nobody told me bro. What the fuck say wake up my man. It's trivia time
Yeah, nobody said shit
I am psyching the post beneath your doubt
Oh my god, I'm so sorry
You are not servants, but seekers carry my light into your shadows and shade your color by number site
She does color by number. All right, but you're gonna tell me when we're playing show of you. I don't know where
Survives every time my path of courage question boldly feel deeply and rise after every fall
You are not servants, but seekers carry my light into your shadows and shape your own ascent
Ghost
Children of the waking one. Oh my gosh. Where is this? I can't find it. Oh my god
Stop
What my pure Lord?
I got it. I got it. I got it. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Carrying my light into your shadows and shape your own. Stop.
They got it.
Pause. Okay.
Be careful. It could be a giant cock. Hey ghost, is that you or somebody else?
It's funny. No, T. Y. always comes up and drops the black heart. Remember that
You even question that that they always form bomb you as ghost and you didn't even question it the T. Y.
You let it appear like nothing black giant heart
Yeah, so go speak. They have an inappropriate name. You can not let them off without speaking like it's me
psyching
If you let that T. Y. up here and they drop another 30 inch black heart
That's on you my man
That's just you know
Okay, hold on a second. Yeah, let me up. Are you gonna make him tall?
Who is that? I can talk. How you doing? That's the black talk. Sorry. That's the black talk
Who is it? Can I can I get the tip of that right now?
No, I can't
Told you both hold on are they using the ghost avatar the T1
And they are
So finally you made your man
Yeah
Oh, let me run one. Can I run one is you guys don't mind? Yeah one shit. You don't even know how to teach page the right way
That's all
Can I shoot her like a princess? I shouldn't trigger like a bit
I can call my best friend I can call psych I can call him I can call him a lot of things
Please friend, please friend. Can you respect page your friend page?
Can I not call I mean I could call sake even gay you wouldn't even worry about it
What do you guys know where I caught her bitch, that's what you guys are worried about. I
Take it back
Good metal board
Hey, okay. Wow. I
Take the bitch part
Ghost
I'm kind of like it takes a bit to irritate me, but like you kind of piss me off
Mean and I'm not going to but like just quit okay
Thank you. Is that okay? Is that okay?
Hey, don't mess with Nadine, is that all right?
Lights, camera, I've left the sprinkle of chili on a chocolate cake.
Don't mess it up here.
That's Nadine, that's...
I just want to say, I want to speak with Chokin, check me out on Chokin, maybe he put a spell on you, I think he just put a spell on you.
What the fuck?
You're fucked, I would stay away from Chokin tomorrow brother.
Yeah, I think it all sucked my dick tomorrow. I don't do like what are they gonna do we're gonna have debate they go
Think it's probably like, you know two inches. So calm down that killer
a little three inch whale
Damn, it's always good to kill fear. They ain't nobody gonna do you guys are all over here trying to test each other's ass
Okay, I'll delete me you seek when you come here ghost
Would you say go ahead babe? What is it that you seek you just judge all of us for being here
What is it that you see because that you acquire to be here my friend my one trench?
I just I'm just here to hang out. Well. I'm also here today
Well, I'll tell you this you're my friend until you're not so if you want to make yourself. I wasn't seeking you
I was it's not all about you. You realize that right? It's not all about you for anyone else. It's always about you
It's not about you though. I wasn't here for you
Gonna make it about me. I'm here for this life. Yeah, it goes if you're here for me
Then please behave yourself and it's like can we move on?
All right, move on have to end the stream. Oh, I'm gonna keep it on for at least 20 more minutes, but let's all have fun
Anybody want to come up? I'll give 100 bucks. Do you keep it on for an hour?
Okay deal
We have
Then that means we have to stay up for an hour if he does that, you know
Yo, what's up girl
I thought you were reading my cards. Did my cards go hard. No, I read your phone call. I didn't my power didn't go out
Clumsies
I'll believe that when I see it clumsy clumsy neater
Hey
I want to hear what she has to say. Can you please guys shut up? Okay? No, we don't like you
What
To project that shit was an hour ago
Let her talk please
And oh no, okay
Alex I do know that okay, I don't know if you want me to say this on here obviously, but I feel like
You're very safe person to be with like your family feel safe
You take care of people you put yourself actually you throw yourself in front of a bullet for someone that you love
You know what I mean? You have this ability to make sure everybody has everything that they need that's around you
And you know you you give the the shirt off your back
You would you know and you're around a lot of people who you've done that for before and in a snowstorm
They had two shirts and you didn't have one and they didn't offer you one
You know what I mean that kind of come I guess
Given take has not been reciprocal forever. It's just kind of come into now where you've chosen and to
Pick and choose where you give yourself to because it's not gotten you everywhere back in the
In your in your past. Yeah, it was it like I tell you the truth when I was young. I was being a dumbass
Yeah, that's what you know
You know what happened to this
She just read my card and it's all positive
No wonder you guys
I asked them exactly I agree
I'm just going off of what my fucking intuitive yeah, I've got nobody asking for a radio besides me dumbass are we that stupid?
Yeah, I'm leaving
I asked you to be quiet and let her talk and you keep interrupting every two seconds. It's like come on. It's like
My bad
You can't keep your composure power 91 seconds
Can you can you at least hear me out? I asked her reading what she was good and everybody else
Everyone was one of getting a reading that she was asked for when it's like she's she's being very gentle
All right good for you guys
Why did why did that asshole have a ski mask on can someone help me out with that one?
What was that about
No, I wouldn't a robbery guy
I'll shut up my bed. I mean if everybody wants a reading. I mean
But you just rub the liquor store you guys are stuck in the reading so we're not on the same page honestly
Oh
They all did he surrounds himself by the law he nestles. I mean that's he had somebody come with me that porn bombs
That many times do you've ever read?
Pillows are poor bombers his knee pillows are poor bomber. He's blanky. He just runs
I'm whatever I'm not gonna make a claim must be here, but whatever
You look the same people up here, I mean you look the same people up here
There's so much and that's all me like I did something wrong. It's I didn't do anything. I have permission to hang out
It's me and you and I guess so man
This kid do I have permission to be your friend do I have permission to fag out my katoa way up up
boy boy
You know that is my katori
This is my fuckers gonna run away better. You don't know actually I get
Gonna be all fucking emotionally gonna run away in this shit. Okay. Jamie's cowboys. Oh
I'll send a crash out Alex. I'm gonna crash out
They're all crying all of them are crying in the chat all of them pray page is crying with a little heart emoji in half
Don't believe that for a second
Yapa
He's crying KZ the homie crying. Jamie's cowboy is crying
It's a fucking crime. Jamie. Yeah, yeah
300 grow the dolphin crying
Psych you know, he's fine
Jesus is anybody not Alice did I not did I not about guys?
He's burger
Somebody better spurred power is channeled by by right. I mean can't have just that silent open panel
It's a link my cock. I'm working shit. How much for you show your mouth Alex
Shut it for me, baby. Oh
No signal what he hit the fucking button on with his fucking for it. No, don't let him back up
That's the whole problem. Why I'm fucking crashing out. Don't let him back up here dumb dumb
Doesn't
Look who's he Apollo your girlfriend here
Think that is is here another one they're popping out of the world work my peeps well
He's a good guy. He's a good guy.
He's a good guy. We got Prairie crying. We got Macatori. Who's easy crying? We got things
that is crying. James Cowboy crying. Wait, wait, wait. You know what, sir? Would you
like a card? Alex, would you like a card, sir? I'm finished off with my deck. Would
you like your card? Oh, please. You're a reader. I'll give you one. I'm not. No, fuck that.
but well not happening
Not getting in
Show your tits here. No, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up?
Oh
The people's podcast TV, too
People
So some kids follow are you there? I mean feet my bad
Tom Tom as Tom dumb dumb
Who's that you don't drop that shit, bro
Who's the mystery guest
You'll be over you already know me
They want sort of be one I'm down to run
Oh
Yo, he ran away aliyah, she
I don't know what I miss psyche. I've been man. How it been. Oh, damn. Yeah
Let's run
I want to play
Then go somewhere else
Ain't nobody's gonna be a good night. He said he was trying to have fun. Let's have fun
The leader right now
Let me run
You feeling you feeling insecure right now because like he's talking to somebody else right now
I got a question everything. I got a question. Let me follow that logic to your mother talking
to you. That Ali has left, bro.
And she's like talking to my little dumb ass.
You have a question, this guy. You got a question, everything? Like, yo, why are you so unprotected?
Every time I say something to psych you, you're like, shout out.
Anything or you can fight, you can do whatever. I think he's being a little jealous.
Yeah, he's getting jealous, he's getting jealous right now.
Okay
Who's a bitch?
You a good boy? Who's a good boy?
Not you.
Who said that?
Who the fuck do you think?
Paige, you sent me fucking white knight, that wizard.
What? None of that made sense.
Well, let me run up with the New York people.
If you don't mind, I'll get back to you.
You have a coffee, motherfucking retard.
I'll let me run up with the New York people if you don't mind.
Do not call me that word. Do not call me that word. It's offensive to most people and I'm not that. Call me something I am.
You're not the fo-fo-fo, babe.
Oh, I said retort. I meant dumb dumb stuff.
You are, man.
Hey, Rose! What's your problem?
Rose!
What's wrong, my man?
What's your problem?
You have an issue with I don't like New York. That's my problem. I don't want to work
She's from Canada. I want all of the smoke big those mom
If you had to drink tonight, so you're not being very you're not being anything
Mom goes you
All you guys all you dumbasses have to say is like
Oh, how much you had to drink? You're not even, you're not even, that's not even an argument.
I could drink it, I could drink it on the table.
What's the argument? I can still make it, dumbass.
Well, when it starts to impact the impact that you have on other people around you,
or anybody, or anything around you, then it's a problem, yeah.
I like to debate, dumbass, you know that. I mean, what's the problem?
I've been this way for two years.
Dumbass, fuck with me, let's go.
I've literally been this way for two years. I'm sorry, you just came up here.
I
You're one funny fuck Lorenzo
I got the I got the I got the
Yeah
I'm gonna go Barry. Let's play. Let's play good. Oh go Barry. What do you want it?
Anybody want it?
That's one one respect respect respect her bro
Yo
Let me run. Let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run, let me run
We love you
Okay, go ahead and make your point. You said
There's no such thing as a queen
Read your fucking dumbass cards
Four cats and two dogs
That's gonna start it in an apartment. So you got little bark. You got the kid
You got a
You walk away, just let them roam and
I got a sunburn. I got a sunburn. What the fuck you took about
So you're old
Alex, what's our crush should we do it or no?
Somebody lives in the trailer first
Oh my god
God damn
You want to do a private one
Pretty hard
Oh
Wow the only two idiots that don't let her talk Apollo and goes
It's fine.
What is she talking about?
Go ahead.
Alex, that's my word.
Stop it, Alex.
You have to actually step the fuck up
to know what I'm talking about to hear me,
to know that, right?
Like, so just a sec.
Yeah, you're gonna go a deck.
What card does the card say?
I'm gonna let you talk.
You're not fucking reading cards, dude.
Yeah.
It's not.
I've been sat there and sat down.
Fucked up, yeah.
God, I'm over the shit.
No, they did it on TPP's last panel and we just they turn change this picture
Look like a big
And you hear
I'll give you some love, Paolo.
Yo, I swear to God, I swear to God.
What the hell are you doing here?
What's wrong with you?
One time for the one time one time for the one time
Yeah
No
Is on the other phone this one is a different phone is on the other phone
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
For the whole the rest of the time
I did
Page when you like to see my beautiful face
No, say yeah page
I would if you want to show your face, but I know it's good not gonna be your face
What's a job is a hot
You ever seen Star Wars?
That is true, I look like a fucking thumb.
I'm asking things, I do look like a thumb.
Show it.
Would you like to see it?
I don't know.
Abracadabra make a show.
Or disappear.
There you go.
You got that.
What the fuck? What the fuck are you showing?
Bro, what the fuck is that?
Don't ask mother fuckers, dick ghosts
What the fuck are you showing?
What the fuck is that?
Don't ask mother fuckers, dick ghosts
What the fuck are you showing?
That was a big dog
Matter of fact, would you like it would you like to leave sir you like to leave
Would you like me to make you leave dumbass? That's what I'm asking
Dumbass, what you actually knew
Make him believe that, make him believe, make him believe
Make him believe that
And when you come to my shithole, I'm gonna fucking kick your ass out, bitch
Respect, let's go
Make him leave
Okay, what you're fucking fuck up the power shut the fuck up
In you follow goes got more
He come up with my shit. He come up with my shit. You scared come up
You know
And what I do when I come up on there share I fucking and debate all them do I not
Well I did
I don't know why this is going on.
You hear it now, right?
You hear it with LES.
Go ahead.
Explain to him why he has to stop doxing.
Somebody has to explain
Your bottle you be the next one
I'm being. I don't know. I don't know if I knew you guys. Yeah, I can literally call the
people. I'm gonna fucking do that. Go ahead. Don't talk to me. Please. Don't talk to me.
You're going to sit there and shut the fuck up. Aren't you?
I don't think you're going to sit there and shut the fuck up. Aren't you?
Run this
No, I don't know. I should cash up send money and it's gonna send them money
Thank you. Yo, yo, yo, go send them some money. Go send them some of your rich man money than you ever have
Yeah, you're rich man because you're rich man. Yeah. Yeah
Send money your name is Richie Rich
I am rich send your money
What happened?
Go ahead and speak real quick
It's probably my mic
I'm pretty sure it's your wife. Yeah, I have she
Good time is a good time. Can I get the reading?
A one-card reading I don't care what it is. Just tell me what it is
Fuck off. Can you suck a dick?
Fuck a dude in the butt
All right, how about that
Come on ghost. We could do all that everybody
There's one card reading one card
No, you're a porn bomber. You're from New York. You're a dumbass. You don't fuck you're talking about it
You also can't
I'm not taking this negative energy page. I'm focused on the positively
Yeah, you're focused on the fuck you fucks on retard
And
She takes them serious like they actually want to read
Yo, bro, stop talking to her like that, bro
They're making you look like a fool by the way
Yeah, we bring it all that negative energy my car's using fly there, bro
You got the was that so the beaver this is really funny. It's actually very fitting for you
I'm actually excited because it's like this is all about building and like growing. It's like reminds me of the
Pentacles in tarot. It's it's very slow growing slow building
But like very much has like a purpose every single job that you do but for me this means like being the man of the house, you know
Making sure you're providing you're like just just the doing go get her beaver energy and like
Making sure that there's stability and every little nook and cranny is filled so that there's no water that can come in
Do you know I mean like there's if you're a barrier is what I'm trying to do that
Anyways, this is really because this fits with your energy right now
And you know what ghost I don't just fucking read cards dude if you actually came to my channel every once in a while
You wouldn't know that
And I have way too much proof from all of these people and all of this is crazy because I haven't upgraded my house
Fortified
Okay
So hard worker loyal tireless of them first
No, this is great. This does correlate so much with like, you know the other day
I got to give you just a short reading like this, which I told you at my link and I'll give you my email
So we can do this personally because there's a lot more to unveil
But like this for you is perfect right now
You've done so much work and I brought this up before and in not only just like in your physical life
But like on the inside and in the inside of others. It's like hearts. It's like repairing hearts in your home
Okay, so
The Beaver personality is a welcome sight.
These good nature and dependable creatures have infinite love and enthusiasm for family.
expressed it by way of earth element. Providing a home, financial stability, and
all that comes after. Although a Beaver doesn't usually initiate a project, once
started, that works steadily for weeks, months, or years to see it through to the
end. The Beaver card appears when the task at hand requires your long-term
steady effort. It can also signify that it's time for some karma to like yoga. So
like this is like selfless release. So like do some selfless service because
so much to others and you need to come somewhere on that list of like the the honeydew list in
a sense right you need to nourish yourself you need to it's just so important because if you're
the provider I went to I went to a pantry last week with my cousin to help give him a food
Well, you're just you're you're a provider. You're you're you're a giver, right?
So it's like you need to make sure that you balance out that love that and like it's you just instead of the reciprocation of the bucket filling coming from
Another energy and yours. It's like your own energy to yourself. Does that make sense?
Yeah, in the midst of all of this don't forget about easy is all I'm trying to say
Copy easy nuts. Leasy
I just, it's really hard for me to get through.
Thank you guys, it's actually really difficult for me.
I have a process and I have steps that I take normally.
Holy shit, he left! He left!
Holy shit, yes!
That's why it's quiet.
I have a process and like steps and kind of like a routine when I do my readings
I like to do and say what I have to say first and then use the cards because that's actual channeling
That's that's coming from I don't know anything about most of you guys other than what I get from your energy on here
And what you unveil, you know when we all are all talking or whatever, but like I don't fucking know through through whole no
wall so
The cards are just visual proof for the reading that I normally give
via without the cards first. Does that make sense?
Just what I'm given via scent, sight, smell, all of it.
Spiritual energy, that Bob.
It is, it is.
So I wasn't paying attention to this negative that he was throwing at you.
And I was like, I'm ready for your positive Bob look.
You know what I'm saying?
Yes, well, I'm glad you feel better and I feel bad I ghost I want you to know that like I do care about you
But like you really went too far tonight
You were being a little belligerent and like it's okay, but don't run psyche streaming just got back on again
You know what I mean? Let them roll with it. Let them do the same. That's how we're all here together
That's what we all found each other. Don't forget that bitches
Apollo needs a reading. He needs a reading. Tell me what you feel
Wait, where's my ring
I thought you already have one. I think I was up here together. You had one. No
No, you guys have been together for the past hour and you know it all of us for the past hour
Who the fuck does you call my dumb dumb fucking retard? Let's run one. Do I run one sir?
I miss my really?
I gotta read
All the more, that's right. Okay, that was my meeting. Fuck
Yes
The more he got the butterfly last night. He hated it too. Don't remind me, baby
Easy when you get here. What is it? Yeah, I got the beaver
An experience respectful debates and discussions
This shot goes got me psyche you got me with that one. This is a fish stock was reference. I'm hungry. Fuck you
You know what we have like in Calgary we have this the kubi king and then in another city closer
Further from Calgary. It was called the dog father and they had like those
How'd you reading page? How'd you reading go?
For who okay, I need to like
God bless America he never does
I dedicate this I dedicate this to page
You better not be a porn bomb
Motherfucker, I know you for two years dumbass you think I'm a porn bomb you breach hard
Why don't you sit there and read your little cards?
Don't do that. She asked you not to call her that you can use that word, okay? Well, she was being assaulting but saying
I'm on the poor mom. I'm like the most
I literally don't need the most I've known you guys for two years
You're gonna show it
My god
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
The first
My fucking finger look at that fucking packet sausage. Fuck on me
Go
I'm hoping for you, like wrong country. It's not okay. I need a Canadian
Didn't easy by that
I don't need it, I don't need it, I don't need the money and he bought it, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need the money, I don't need
You can wash yourself dude at least wash yourself before you do shit like that. Can you all rise for the national anthem beige? Oh look you'll turn the stone
What is your feet?
Wait, what is he doing?
Is that a foot or a hoof?
Was that a hoof?
No, we didn't see shit, stupid.
That was a hoof.
Nobody's seen nothing, you heard?
Nobody's seen nothing.
There's hoops in the air, and chicken wings flying on the second floor.
I mean, that's what I'm talking about.
Yo, thing, joint thing.
Joint thing.
Fuck you, fam.
Bag it.
Hey ghost
What is God he joined
Every time he joins, I mean he's God is the problem. Yeah, I'm the problem. Yeah, I'm the biggest problem ever
We can blame God for all
You can but he doesn't care
Okay, oh you motherfucker. She just said you're really nice
The best ever I mean nothing nothing maybe but he has a very nice guy who never are used
He's never a piece of shit. He's never a digener. Never a dumbass
So I don't have to look at those hoops again. Can we put in so much?
Can we get the feathers in the air? Can we just spread it out get the wings going like?
Well, fuck it. I'll run it. Hey, how much money you got? I'll run what five bucks. It's like he's so I key
Tell me they cash up you five bucks. I'm just tell me tell me where in the world would you catch a priest in a speedo?
If you'd like to see my face by the way
It's the best
Somebody said he showed a finger
Can I say that
God and page can rule. I'm gonna be a farm with ghosts and uh, what's a dumb ass a dumb down there? Yeah
Don't smell any anti who say
Everybody yeah dumb ass is fucking I didn't say it
the
No
She's
I would actually start my panel with my face she never fuck out of here with all these rules, dude
You said you'd buy the painting
I've never once said that dumbass
And a panel dumbass what do you mean?
That's like don't with a bunch of fucking retards. You're a fucking liar
Just say you're a fucking liar. I'm not a liar sir. I never cuz I never once
Yo, never once said that don't boss off
I'll put my face
You heard
Thanks guys impression a ghost
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
They go by the way, you're fucking average towards missing
On the phone, I can see but now the big she never sent away
That means I'm being shut up and
so you also are a faggot
who wants one
look at this
you're gonna let them call me a faggot
that's a hate stream
You run a hate stream
Say it again bag it okay ghost I'm not gonna stand for this has it been an hour. I think it's been an hour
What does that mean? It's been an hour. What is what I mean around the panel for another hour
Oh, wait, did you know you said if I ran the power for an hour or something
You want to say faggot go ahead you paid for it
I don't know a second you just said it
This is a good one am I getting bullied before you said it
Well, you're the thing again
Say why you said it again, so I'm getting bullied
You're the thing
He said it last I didn't he literally said it
I'm a gay guy. You're supposed to sit down my panel. Yeah, but you're not a faggot
You're not faggot
Let's respect the panel come on set enough
Say maggot don't say the other one
You can't get I'm leaving I swear
What are you sharing, you faggot?
I promise I swear
Where the god I'm done
Go nuts
No, I'm not gonna say it. I told you I'm not gonna say it. I'm not gonna say it. I told you I'm not gonna say it.
Don't fucking say it.
Golly, you're being such an interviewer.
Can I call...
Don't even say it.
Can I say the B word?
And I don't mean bitch. Can I say beautiful?
And I want to direct that to Gaby, if you don't mind.
Thank you.
Sorry, babe.
I knew you would.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Agreed, it's fine.
Because Paige simps over me, you ever noticed that Goddy, like, she simps.
Well, when she saw your foot.
I heard I started fangirling when she saw your foot.
Yeah, she simped in Paige. I'm not interested, okay?
Back off.
Can you imagine if you showed his face? Oh my God, Paige would be all over the fucking floor.
Oh, I look like a thug.
She'll faint, she'll faint, she'll faint.
She definitely likes a thug, man.
Get down!
Okay
Not paid. I'm just letting you know goes is not interested. So stop turn
Okay, bitch you draw mustache on yourself with the black market
Maybe a little goatee
Goatee
Yeah, this gotta be washable
So no sage, huh?
That's a no on the sage
Wait, yeah, Moncato spirit. Oh, that's cute. I like that. Yeah, that's nice. That's nice
But you know, I know
Is that a dreamcatcher?
Like a long don't give it don't get my
I swear to God I'm about to go fucking a pin this fucking place
I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing my I'm losing
Hang your bed like weird shit. I don't know. I love you, but the dream catcher
Yeah, one down there dreamcatcher
Fucking assholes
Easy as the tattoo of the fucking dreamcatcher
He
Remember when he said he's gonna go home to
He was gonna
Dude, it's one thing if a girl has one, but if a guy has one, oh man, that's how I say the g word
Gage it right there. That's the worst
Jesus
Hey, why are you crashing out?
double
Pigeon crashing off what happened page. Yeah, you did the mustache you left. What happened?
Oh, I didn't make it to life with a dream catcher. You don't have to show the dream catcher. There you go. That's perfect
Why are you crashing down
You use that shit like you're my you're the dream catcher that is good. That's a good one, right?
You're my dream
Would you like to take one more shot you all the dream catcher page?
And that's it. It's fucking just
What'd you like?
We'd like to take one more shot. Is that somebody we know?
Ghost Aronies
The picture that you draw
She's got a Cuban and Italian flag on her butt cheek, so you're just gonna have those
Why are you why are you doing porno pictures of someone?
For a calendar
He's a movement away
I'll take a moment. Oh, no, no, no, hold on. You're doing it. You're doing a funny
That's right. They're getting them
Getting it out and i'll probably jump down because i'm getting a little bit too much negative energy like it built up and now i'm going to cut some of my energy.
Oh you're going to blame it on your internet but now you're asking me.
I told you like some sage.
Bitch tell me it's beautiful.
You laughed on purpose.
Don't fucking blame it on your internet.
It's the poem dude.
The poem brings negative energy whenever it comes to it.
They're dropping on the spot.
It's like an idiot.
Listen to him.
He's complaining already.
He want to be up here.
Dude call me a bitch one more fucking time.
Who called you a bitch?
Ghost cut the shit man.
Well, I said that's what I meant was for my better
Yeah, okay
Fat fuck
Oh, tell him tell him up on him
Very good
Can I ask you a question Alex
Well, it's your
No, we're getting punished it over
What's that?
Why are you telling me to be white?
Why are you telling me to be white, Alexander?
God, he's not saying that.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not saying that.
I'm gonna ban you.
That you're a bitch?
No, the whole world knows that I'm white, Alexander, because of you.
No, because of you. You're white, aren't you? I am
Babbage my paves I'm gonna ban you pay for this
I'm gonna ban you sir shut up
I will get me please
Eleven
Yeah
What were you saying go ahead? Yo, you sure you told again how what's wrong with you bro?
They look like women's feet like fat women's feet
It's page and back I'll get $50 in dumb ass faggot. You don't even know
People that just said
Dumbass all smack you in the face
You got a fucking problem
What do you what I just said repeated back to you pay ten dollars and I'll repeat it
You're too stupid to have a conversation with me.
Pay the fuck to be a doctor in here.
I'm dealing with a fucking bunch of dead jerks.
Are you gay for free?
Never.
I mean, I'd bet that's just why I do it.
This page doesn't come back.
Yeah, you better pray some girl comes back because it's starting to sound like a day date come back
For your color of bitch again, dude, yeah
Fuck you color of bitch
Of all people you go to go
They just the best
I don't think I'm gonna see home showing free
Who's in the middle
Put the heart back
So what happened to the Apollo and last did you get that shit out of Apollo did you tell us how you feel about him I
You won't listen
You wanted to ban you
And I told you he can't even come in understand
Each other yeah, I could see that
You told me to change the name you caused orders Apollo with your little
trolling and antics and then say I was just joking
And then Godian, you know, God wasn't even there.
Alex and whoever made him do it, huh?
You did it.
Now stop nothing.
You and Chris convinced him to do it.
After you put the idea in the head.
What did you do?
In your head, in your head, not in this head, in your head.
It was a good idea, Dick. It was a good idea. What are you hoping to do?
Stop manipulating these people.
What happened and I won't go that was perfect
Apollo typed in the chat you renamed the federal TV B2 and then
Like do it do you motherfucker? Holy shit facility on earth
And he did it
So who's to blame there? I think it was a team effort right team. No
Yes
If I tell you to jump over bridge, would you do it?
It depends
This was your plan to change this place
That's it. We're there. They're gone. No, for me, for me, for me, it was that's it shows how easy it is to
manipulate someone
Manipulate a low IQ people all this big mouth blah blah blah and deep down
zero IQ
So you should be thanking me because you didn't manipulate shit. We did
We took your idea and we know you did
And you can't imagine even in it like you can manipulate LS
We didn't manipulate we just nudged you did you didn't know we nudged and
I you know he wanted it. He would have said no no. I'm not doing that. He was like hell. Yeah, they go
For me it was perfect example how how easy it is to manipulate all these
Learned from you
Yeah
You keep your style body keep your style you don't do it. I have my copy you I had this changed it up a little bit, but
It's all due to you
Remember when you told me to come troll psyche about six months ago you told me to come troll the channel
Shut up you told me to make you do you told me to make them week so you can come in and take over remember that
Here we are
TPP to everybody
Did you win you won? Yeah, good job. He's not even up there. There's the three of us
I'm just happy to have my job back for all security
Oh, yeah, you are TV security. No, well, it's the second one, but who cares?
Jesus, did you see that Jack anywhere? I didn't even think they made jackets that size
Was that like 10 XL
Who
For no less army on the spot, bro. I didn't have to drop a resume. I come on recommend my man Bruno security jacket
It's huge. Oh, it's fat shit. Yeah
Army Navy store like in the fucking television army, but here you go Bruno. We just found this in the dumpster
Damn that thing's huge man. It's like a parachute
Security
No, I never seen security hide so much in my life
He has at the ball
He's hiding across the street at the restaurant
Because that's how he feels
Bruno's ashamed of them. He's a white guy from Long Island
He doesn't want to be seen with Dominicans with their pants around their head
No
No, seriously, why are you right in every video like you're being a student?
He's out like I don't know these fucking
Are you black are you black Alexander?
What are you black?
You hate white people so much, I don't understand why
I love white people
No, you don't those are my people. You can even say that with a straight face. I
Love white people
Let me try again for the top and action you haven't
You haven't exposed me to be white and I know we because I'm white
Because I'm why what?
Paul you're not even white dude
I
Mexican or something, bro. He's just fooling all of us. He's not with Germany
He's
That's why he's always looking for rain
You're not an Aztec warrior Apollo
Yeah, I'm not I
Wish I wear one then then uh, I would be more attracted to to the rain, you know, I
Called you though, I call your forehead your way to whatever
You were you sit in dog. You said in a dark room funny computer
That's crazy. That's a problem
You sit in a dark room like a loser your choice Babbage that's my first wait a second
Wait a second before I forget before I forget. I gotta talk to psyche psyche. Can you come up here real quick, please?
I before I forget
It's better if you're listening
That's you buddy get up here. It's like you get up here. I don't know. I don't I see we're gonna dress in this you
Where is he when he falls asleep? Yeah, move the horn out of the way my man other fucking get up here
Yeah, after all of you call it him the f word all over and over now we were calling ghost. Yeah, we're not you oh
Oh
Thing that is they got moist what?
He hasn't been open a lot thing that is he's not allowed
Be the told him you're not allowed to go up there anymore
Sike sake you get up here. I gotta tell you something get up here
Something you did what do you do what do you do? I'll tell him when he gets in here
no, tell me first, I want to learn
no, no, no, this is a big deal
oh, man, how big, can't be bigger than the old McQueen scandal
he's talking mad shit about me
about you?
yeah
more than me?
we're gonna address this
I told you last night, UJT and Rain took his panel down
more than that?
no, no, no, it's something about, something different
Well, he's not even listening
Do with that Alex so mouse big stuff with talking big stuff
Why don't you say about God he got so bitter find out you said something bad about him
Thank you. Get up there, dude. Get up here, pal. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You know what? He's a bunch of a bunch of a bunch of fucking
friends. Yeah. He talked shit about me too. How you had as bad as
he did about you. Who wants to run more big guys here?
I don't know, that's what he does, I guess, talk shit.
He's playing with his fucking phone down there, you see him?
What do you say, man? Run it back. I'll let's see them other parts of the way
He just let me back up here. Did he buy my bullshit and ride along with it? Like no
Nobody found nothing. He might be back up here. Now you're just fucking shit
That's not boy come it down my man
It's a little hype, but he does get a little hype. You notice that
I'm like a fucking beef jerky or something. They cool up
You know what he does? First he gets rid of the girls
He chits on all the girls when they leave and then he gets hyper when all the guys are up here
Mm-hmm. He's got to be the top dog
It's the hot dog. No, the big top hot dog. He's got a like a
He's a Nathan's he's a Nathan's fat hot dog
Yeah, we see the toes again bro because now one fucking nugget
If I ask nicely or show them that's game
I swear God I will be getting a gate. I can get up here. What'd you say about God?
Don't don't be a chicken shit get up here. Oh, well you saw his legs
No, I know that's lucky
Alright ghost you chased away
Situations psych say please you got a problem with how I treat your guests on the panel
Yeah, yeah, fuck you
Tell me why you have a problem with how I treat your guests on the panel and you might be a faggot. I don't know
I'm talking to you
Oh, I heard you have a problem how I treat your guests on the panel
Yeah, you've been very difficult this whole night
I
Thought I was very respectful to your guess
I had a feeling it was about her, but why would that even come up?
She might be an effort um because I was I went to
I got my channel got
She's like, oh my god because probably because I think she's like she's a god
You probably try to kick it down or something like that and I was like no but uh, she's like oh those people are mean or something but
I don't know, it's not a big deal.
I want everyone to feel respected and there's different people with different shapes and
bodies and everything and I would like not people want to be maybe comfortable because
they're physical appearance and so I know you but I know it's part of your stick.
I already have foam.
Okay, okay, so we squashed it.
Yeah, it's squashed.
What a problem.
I don't need a squash.
Okay, it wasn't an issue that
Don't ask a person no one's fighting
No, it's over. What the fuck?
What's wrong with him?
What do you think he's going to be a war?
Yo, Paolo, you piece of shit.
Hey, you fucking annoying KZ, you fucking annoying KZ.
You're fucking annoying KZ in the chat.
Stop it.
Just say who it is, or like, don't talk about them.
I don't care.
You're just being cryptic.
Like, I'm going to say, who, who, who,
and I don't want to sound like an owl, OK?
Oh, he always does that.
Casey start starting shit. He's like he has a mystery about
Bad nothing about here. I
apology here
Say it or don't say
Well, my paul is gone. Yes, pardon blood. Yeah, what oh, they're here in the chat. Let me see who is you know
What when ocean can I say that we were
Dumb dumb
Very rude to me. Joni's here. Oh, wow
Party started with Joni here
Joni get up here. I gotta tell you something
Hurry up. I don't have all day
I'll tell her she out. Can I tell her if she even here? I don't think she's here
Oh, she left a little bit ago. That was like 15 minutes. Oh, that was all I'd be retarded
Yeah
So you'll care if less stabs somebody okay Apollo I you had your chance to tell the guy instead of straight, but you don't care
Yeah, Paulie not here dumbass
He's right there
My that's fun follow I guarantee that dude
Now lots around something
May well
Jesus, this guy is totally drunk.
Shut up, Apollo. Shut up.
You have no argument. Just sit there.
Be a good boy. Who is a good boy?
Well
That sounds good doesn't
I'm gonna have a recharge in there, but I like it
Power
What? What do you want? What do you want? Answer dumbass or say big dog. My answer is no. My answer is no. I'm going to leave this guy out.
You got a red dog yet?
I'm finna say a swear word.
Why don't say it. Don't say it. Don't say if you say I don't think it's going to say or something
I'm gonna leave
Do you want me to say it? No, don't say it
Yeah, don't fucking say it. Yeah, you've been warned. Mm-hmm. I'm caught
I'm finna say it.
Don't say it, ghost.
Oh, okay.
Can you say, can you say ghost always wins?
No.
No, no, no, no, you better say it.
I'm finna say it, yeah?
Say ghost always wins, no.
Oh, I'm finna say it.
Oh
Yo, do you why?
Tyler, what do you want? What do you want me man? You mean which one is it?
What do you want me?
What's your last name it shall be tall. She'll be Tony Bologna. Do you like you want to see exactly ghost Bologna?
We know you're looking
Me you want Alex?
Yeah, I'm gonna say it. Yeah
Dumb Dumps there you go
Yeah
I mean
You'll miss it
I'm not as great as
No, there we go
I know
Did it work? Yeah, it worked. Can I say it? All right, that's good
Yeah, I don't know why
I can at least say one word, right?
Yeah, man, if I say it
Page I'm
Usually like this he only gets like this when he's around certain people
Can I say you're glad to pass or not? I'm tired of apologizing for you fucking ghost
What are you you know what you did?
You know what the fuck you did
What's up? Stop the signal and game you're fucking doing everybody. I'm what what did I do you know?
Just apologize. Oh often. I do it now. Don't do it
I
I'm not gonna do it. It's like I paid for this. I'm gonna experience it
Have to go
Get the fuck out that see what you did not sir you made a poll leaf
What up in your fucking microphone, dude
I don't know why I don't know why
I don't know why
You're going to break our bond as brothers our brotherhood bond will be broken if I hear you or a bit example
That's a bedtime story
All that time story the once upon a time
There was a there was a guest
Hey, did you come back? Is it there? He was a big can I tell them that?
You have to treat her like she's a little bit there and go ahead. I was a little guy to go ahead. I can tell
Turn so
Once upon a time you shut the fuck up. I mean imagine that shut up
Nightingale
You get the nightingale car, though
Yeah, oh you really want to compare that
People well, I'm not going to say a word
I'm on strike
Yeah, I'm not gonna say a word until you come back page forget it. I'm not gonna talk
Rob I have the monkey
Okay, baby hit the link and you can cook and stuff your face on the panel with us
So I'm a boy with God
Hey, you come back
You can blame it. Oh
I'm not gonna zone you up
Hey, you come back
God forbid God's gold is to green eyes.
Little green eyes done.
That cost money, what cost money, babe?
What cost money?
Is there even a link?
Oh, she wants money.
Ghosts at your department.
You know what to do, ghost.
No, she won't be money
She wants to suck me she could suck on this fucking dick here
Okay, it's anywhere from a year pizza, okay now you're talking
Let's see this. Did you make this pizza?
No, pizza is involved here.
Let's see this pizza.
Okay.
I don't know. Pizza makes you want to take your own eat.
She makes your own pizza sometimes.
No.
There's a door.
Let me see.
Let me talk.
Canadian pizza.
One, two, three, four, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five, six, five
That fuck was like I got all yours. You know, he's fine. He does got all yours
Fuck everybody
Back in the day
That's square school pizza. I want the middle piece. I don't want that side shit
No crust
You know, it's the best, oh, it's a deluxe, a deluxe, I had stuff crest myself.
Who's this?
Oh, who's at the door?
It's Raimundo.
Who's Raimundo?
Raimundo, pal.
Raimundo, speak up.
Gotti, how are you doing there? Hey, buddy, how you been man? Gotti? How's everything there, man?
I'm calling in from the you know Raymondo. Yeah, that's Raymundo. How do you do a man?
Calling in from TPP man. They got a lot to say about you. All right
P2 my man. Well, I'm a brother but they do
Now Alex didn't bring you up. Not one second. Honestly. Oh good. Good. That's the bus. That's good news
Alex, I'll be honest. I wish I could play Minecraft with you so I could put a bullet in your head
What's going on got he was going on guy you got me I only you would do some shit like this
We're in moon the whole time. I know that face. That's Jimmy neutron
Right
I don't know if you know who BG is here in the community. He looks like
BG's a bitch. He looks like a seed from Toy Story
that's a good story there you go the sick kid that torches the toys that's right
that's the black small pack oh my god that's you motherfuckers
oh it is that kid that's fucking kid that's him that's the sick fucker from Toy Story 1
what's going on guy to yo guy what the fuck you do over there to jason man you got you got the
community over there all stirred up again are you kidding me they're still talking about me over there
what's going on
I don't know, they brought you up, they were like,
oh yeah, he's a fucking piece of shit.
He's always loving the drama.
Sometimes he comes in, you know, he's acting cordial.
And then, boom, I don't know, he's just taking shots.
They said that today?
They said this about four days ago?
I haven't been over there in like two months.
In relation to Telemundo?
I'm gonna have to go back and say,
why are you talking shit about me?
Hey, yep, yep, I won't bring you up, but thank you. You could bring you could bring up bring moon though
Bring moon. No, tell me all about it
Where's the good old yeah, I've had it you see it's too boring over there. There's no fun
Oh, it's how it's fucking boring shit. Yeah, people go there to die
For real for him, man. What do I want? Do I want to hear about Randy's dog dying? I don't think so
You fuck it's always the same shit you fucking call in and you hear Mary fucking talking about food
You hear fucking fire fire calling in. Oh, man
He's a sick fuck. He loves it. And then you got to hear about Angie complaining about everything. Yeah
And then Queen Queen T what's the last thing that happened between Queen T and a JC?
Ah, I guess she she was taking Wigan's side and JC didn't like it
Shit, and then she told Mena that she hoped that her husband dies
He's in the army. Oh my god. Yeah, she was she flips out and then she hates all Trump supporters all that shit
And then I think JC had enough and said fuck this bitch
Yeah
It's awesome
Yeah, I'm gonna let you guys go. I'm gonna call right back psyche. Oh, where are you f a ggot? Come on man speak up
We come from the closet
Great call
That was very Mundo from TPP
live from rey mundo buenas noches rey mundo muchas gracias everybody give it up to rey mundo
rey mundo from telamundo telamundo he's the love telamundo you ever watched telamundo
Yeah, it was
Women on earth the best the fucking it's a commercial everything
What do they get these women from this?
Sure, they have their show called Laura Laura
And they start fighting with each other in fucking
Fucking watermelon dick sitting there like in between them
Like what the fuck this blooter has these supermodels fighting over him. Exactly. What's going on, baby?
If they saw me like this little shithead loser, what a mother faggot.
That's these supermodels.
They're a game show called The Twelve Corazones.
So
You do the ugly dude in the 12 beautiful women a party went to all the supply of lipstick just in that one show alone
Right lipstick the whole supply on the planet party if you the stock market and lipstick bro with that show is on
Well, of course, I'm so nice. Holy shit. You couldn't eat my man.
Dude, that's just a lot. What about Washington Mercado? Remember the freak, the psychic dude?
Almost like a psychic. Oh, the psychic dude, yeah. Basically psychic. Pretty much psychic Mercado. Psychic Mercado.
You remember Washington Mercado, baby. Holy shit.
You my man had the corner for he cornered the market in mucho mucho amor
You remember that again, that's for the site
There's old psychics with a shit fucking miss Cleo
Miss Cleo, no miss Cleo fucking know Alexandra Mayers and wafter McDonald's like he she made fucking bank
She was like the original
just line of people right
Yeah, like yeah, like you got something coming with you, you know
Will I ever find love?
Yes, just call me now
Only files a minute will be on the phone for half hour
It would have put a hundred up Bill
Like these you report the site my man has a whole thing going with
Like you need a 900 number
Way not more bro. He's got like nine hundred nine hundred numbers going my man
I'm not a psyche awakens. He's gonna go with the psyche calm. You will see
a menu from $0.99 to $3,000,000, $99,000.
If you want photocyte key, you know,
there's all different half hour calling from the photocyte,
the ministry, the court.
You know ghosts will be the first caller, right?
Hey, so what's this money gonna buy him out? What's this gonna buy his whole shit out?
Here we go
You need to pick you with a crystal ball. Yeah, well
If you know
Trackable
Just put a garage and don't pay the garage and you're in there
Wow, you really did some work
extreme
Door what do we got here and people are gonna fall for this shit, bro
People love the stuff people all ladies
Psychopathic gonna be the coldest
Well, let me see chicken like a psyche in a Ferrari in six months, bro
Should I ask my boss if I'm gonna get a raise this week. Yeah. Yeah, you should go ahead and do it like it
Don't forget me for stock a boy
Don't forget where I send the food to the house, buddy
You wouldn't be able to come on my temple set my man. You're cold bastard you
Let's go out on a limb and say Emma Leviathan is not cute
She's not just not at all. I'll fuck her
Especially drunk. I wouldn't know no wrong guy was drunk drunk. She has a nice body
I'll fuck her like direct out of my mind when they like after parties again, whatever, you know drunk like so
Like yeah, but no doesn't turn me on at all pretty weird one
Who's that one? He's in love with what's the name of that other one?
Well, that's what made some weird the pig. Who's that pig one that he loves that was from the house
Piranha, no
I run is the fat ass from Canada. You're not talking about fucking the crazy bitch. Yeah, the one from the house stint show
No, I'll fuck her too, but she's also not like like hi
She had a facelift. I don't know what she did. Oh, she's like a Karen face
Yeah, she's
You throw a bang to shut her up
Exactly the bang I'll throw a bang especially if you're on one night after dinner
Oh, fuck double hundred percent of throw a bang
You know Johnny a bang after Johnny a bang baby. Johnny needs a couple banks
Johnny I don't I don't think I can handle Johnny
That laugh would drive me nuts.
You would end up in the river like an old loggy.
We would kill her.
Shut up you psycho bitch.
You're a demon from my house.
We would end up on a fucking Netflix special.
Good thing she's not here man.
We wouldn't hear the end of it.
Yeah, we'd be dead.
She'd be up here for a few seconds.
Thank you.
Erase this part.
Let Joanie hear that.
The next thing you know there's a recording and she thought she heard something
She didn't want to come tonight she said because we were too vulgar Johnny wasn't me. It wasn't me. It was that other guy
It was it was I
We talked about mango toys
Mangle. What's up? Did this pizza get cooked yet page? What we're waiting on your pizza. Yeah, what the fuck?
I see this pizza. I want to see this pizza
Pete's she's cooking in one of her cats and nobody burns sage, which really her nobody
Right when we never asked for sage burning and they're just saging it up like oh
I haven't seen saying burned up here in like three months
And they ignored it they laughed in my face like what is that loser?
No Sage at all
Oh, these are old comments, okay
KZ, what's wrong there? I thought he got banned from here
Who's vapid horror I love that name
Rapid or bag Vapido horror Vapida or rapid or bag
Vapido de hora
Vapido de 12 corazones
Tell the world
What about Sabado gigante remember that one?
I don't think that's it
More horny than that that
I see you all the time
The ugliest Paris piece of shit on earth
Sabado he got him
On the show the other girls have to kiss the most they're fired. That's crazy
You know he fucked all of them. Oh, yeah
He must have had a hang on to himself right at them Domingo Tuesday hang on to baby use the Spanish Bob Barker that guy
No, he was the Spanish you have no emba water
Yeah, sabato. He can't tell you what though. Oh
Tell him
Ecuadorian fucking immigrants just supermodel bitches, and he was like yeah, I'll give you a dream
That's good shit. I wonder what that shit now. They don't still there anymore. It's over, right?
Yeah, it's over a CIA court on like this is this some should not be around humanity
Oh, that's boring
You're a big capital he got a used to us. Oh, fuck. Yeah, I used to love that
Learned all my Spanish that I don't know
That's how you catch up on your Spanish
Illetevello remember that one illetevello. No, it was another game show that he let him a low. No
They used to sing it every time they said it
Illetevello, I know that
you mean yeah so you spent half your life watching channel 47 I love the fucking
vision look at page is going after KZ in the chat whoa whoa whoa she's gonna
vicious look at this get her get him page get him she has said a lot of
terrible things to me page she's my sister like I said pipe down now bitch you
don't know who she is
If you have an issue, it's not the place motherfucker
Yes, I do read energy. I am not to be fooled fool
Please stay out page. Why are you involving yourself you that lonely?
Whoa, she's about to cut you fool quit airing a KZ. That's enough motherfucker
Whoa, they love
They're going at it. Oh, yeah, who is she?
Look at the thing that is
He's dead shitless
Take that is trying to insert itself in between like hey, yeah, look at me
I'm perfectly lonely by choice bitch. Would you like to go motherfucker? Let's go
None of these places could hit the link
They were both
Typing with the thumb means abuse
That's so funny to me to the abuse drop to below 20 yet
Shit bless you, bless you man bless
By John Yankee
420 hit the link you're welcome if there's a link is there you know fucking link
Why do I know the same Bayesian Yankee?
By any Yankee is my friend's wife
You know Stephen King someone eat you might even king that motherfucker threatened me. Yeah
That's his wife. Yeah, you kidding me in real life. I'm kidding. You're not in real life
But do you know what I'm talking about Stephen King? Get your beige and ass up here, bitch. We got beef. Let's go
We got peace. Yeah, you're going to cross the beef, baby. No man's letting me we're gonna handle it round now me
Hold on. Is it the same Stephen King though?
Don't think that's her dude. It is her sure but better first of all is the same Steven King
Oh, wait a second pages man. She's about to show the pizza page come on up. Hey, you come back. Thank you. Let her up
There we go
I'm not going to show you my pizza. I'm up here to say what I need to tell me to come up. I'm not
You're not here to show you. You came up here on false pretenses. Oh guys. What's that the door? It's me psyche
It's that dude. It's that guy's ziled
Yo, which I got up. Oh, Sydney. What up, kid?
I want pizza. I know she pleased us with the pizza then she came up here to trash on KZ
Well, your car is even catching it all over the place lately
Look who's in the chat that dude. Um, what's his name fucking no raging demon?
Raging demon
Never be to made up. So let's not bring that up. We're not gonna bring nothing up. We should probably not also KZ
You need to keep her name out of your mouth cuz you just don't need to be airing anything
And if you have problem you probably talk to her and yeah
I'm gonna stick up for her cuz girls got a stick together and she's a very nice fucking girl
And I do know her so shut your mouth say it all gangsta like I said it earlier
What do you how do you want me to say it add a little motherfuckers and bitches in there keep talking about sweepy
And I pop a fucking cap in your ass
Oh shit
It's on a rampage. You can turn it down with those a little too extreme
Astrology thing, I think right now we're in retrograde. I'm just kidding
Wait a minute on the fucking moon. Oh
Yeah, I always do a clumsy here looking like a rapper. What's that man? How you doing page?
Shalom, bro. I need it
Are y'all doing everybody's awake at this hour
Yeah, because we're all psychotic
Motherfuckers we need meds vampires
Anybody got pain meds? Yeah, I mean meds. I like psychotic
Were you doing a reading this page my bad if I interrupt no, it's okay
I wasn't because it was earlier, but it kind of fucking
Technically she was she was reading KZ for filth
I just I did come up here for once for like the first time ever to kind of just cook and to silence somebody
Before they fucking lose privileges of being fucking here in general
Was good to see you Paige. Well, you too. It's a very nice scarf
Thank you, you're welcome. He knitted himself
Yeah
You sent this to me because you told me you needed this with every stitch of love
Did you get the the lip marks on it that I put on there?
Is that what that smell was yeah
Yeah, I don't really care it's not meant to bother you it was just a statement just take it how you fucking will
No, he'll never let this go. I don't care
And I don't cook. I don't come up here to do that normally
But like just just keep other people's name on your mouth
And like and it was just in a different intended context like it was very whiny
And it was very like oh, me and it's not very manly and I don't care how you roll in your personal life
but like don't fuck around with people that have been here and like don't deserve that shit and
Every once in a while you're gonna run into somebody who disagrees with you. So here we are
Excellent one you have to fix your avatar. It's a nipple
All right. I appreciate you.
Why? I was trying to let you let it out and just freeze it in there.
Appreciate you, Alex.
Good. I hope you're speaking. All right. I'm just saying.
I'll have all of your back in the same instance.
Like, fucking, I don't really know that I wouldn't say behind your back
that I wouldn't say to your face, you know?
Oh my god.
Still a nipple, my man. It's still a nipple. Yeah, I'll fix it. I like some fix it. All right.
What nipple? I don't see a nipple. It's the white circle tree of that roof.
Whatever they're called. Yeah. It's still a nipple. I don't lie to my boys. Oh, now it's an X. There you go.
For your page, I think clumsy is hurt because he wanted a reading
Right. He was like miss page
No, I was
She was up here doing her little card thing. I just wasn't I know when you missed out and he missed out on his reading
Well, that's kind of I can't that's like being like everyone else got suckers today, but you don't get one because you were late
Fuck she's giving suckers out what you give us suckers to suckers
I don't know. I guess I'm gonna get a happy male fuck a sucker. Oh happy males. Yeah
You guys have those weird, okay
We have this strange thing and I do not like the combination and I think it's suspicious
So listen, I don't trust it the combination of the KFC and
Fucking Taco Bell or time or whatever we have here in Canada. I think it's weird. That's for fat people
Yeah, no, we have that too. We have fucking people. Yeah, we have the biggest whales. I like
No, I got it. I got a KFC Taco Bell and it's got a
I went to one KFC buffet one time
With my brother, but you're not bad enough in the fucking food fight everybody's throwing chicken all over the fucking place
I couldn't fucking believe it. I'm not gonna lie the Popeyes from KFC are actually fucking very underrated, bro
Those fuckers are bomb
Bomb is has to be fresh though
Has to be has to be can't be sitting at oil all fucking day. It tastes like shit
Mm-hmm
Get all like mushy and shit like that. Yeah
All the hard wings that you can't even bite into
I mean, this might be a lot of people, but like Taco Bell has him like that's not my place to ever eat a bro
It's just I don't like the way it tastes at all. I think the only thing I'll probably eat from there is like a
Chalupa or a gordita. That's it. It's not me. I like the chalupa and they had to excel grill stuff burrito that they got
Who's who's James with throw
He's he's he's good people. He's
He's known for for being on
in his wife pretty much. Power
in him on. Is she hot? Where's
the pizza?
is she hot?
you ate it already?
she has a beautiful heart
who's at the door?
that means she's not hot
that's a nice way of saying she's ugly
hey Jimmy, what's up kid?
I'm always, I mean
Jimbo, Jimbo, my man Jimbo
what's up?
no cock in your hand right Jimbo?
no cock in the hand
You guys know this guy. Yeah, I saw him on 42nd
We're psychic
Who's playing music
Can you fix that bullshit
It's first time on a panel. You gotta come some slack. Oh
She's got the cards up for your clumps. I
Was just about to say you do see her shuffling right guys. Oh, oh
Let's get ready. You use the way you know when those about to get reading
I'm always interested in those in those read. I'm not gonna lie like when you when you hear other people's readings
And when you guess like right on the spot
That makes like other people like getting into a lot more because I don't know
I I was watching a video about like I guess something has to do with terror reading
But also it has to do with like I guess like a different type of terror reading
Is there a reading I guess like dark and then I guess there's like good spirit like good terror reading bad terror reading
Is that sure?
How does all that work? Hmm. What do you got is that you what do you just say? I haven't moved here
And then like good terror reading, you know, like yeah, that's good and negative
Yeah, page focuses on the positive though. Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course, of course
But I will tell you the negative. I'm not like gonna fucking sugarcoat shit either. Yeah
The documentary I was like watching about the terrarium like they were like, that's all based on your energy crazy
I was like hold on. I was like psyching and don't do that type of shit like
The fuck oh, but that's so it should be like that. I mean if something bad is gonna happen, they should let you know
No, of course, of course, but the way they were doing their readings and they had to do with like
Not I can't put energy off on you, bro. It's all about your energy
Exactly exactly that's pretty much what they were trying to like get off. I guess the throw off their energy. I
Don't know. I'm new to this shit, bro
I don't know I think we're from medium ways or not. I'm making page happy. We have to get more serious about this
It's okay. I'm just channeling right now. I'm just writing things down now. He is what she does her stuff. Thank God. Thank God. I
don't know
Okay, so
Without cards I have to say
There's a lot coming to me and it's because you have not I don't think you obviously have don't get readings all the time or anything and
there's a lot of, I don't think that you,
maybe as of lately, you've been listening more
and trying to pay attention to like,
like say signs and synchronicities and whatnot,
but normally I feel like you're,
when you get in, how do I explain this?
You're so fast paced that it's hard for you,
or hard for messages to come into you
because you're not paying attention.
So when you get, it's like a bit,
see what I mean?
Like it's hard to, there's so much going on.
Okay, I do have someone coming through though.
I don't know what you call your grandma or great-grandma, I'm not sure who she is yet.
I just met her.
But then there's these like, okay, so tropical fruits, grilling, back your parties.
I feel like there's so many, like you're something that you're trying to go get around.
It's like trying to get around something without-
Uh, what is it?
Getting the hair of your chinny chin chin kind of like getting around something in a sense,
but you're doing it in a way that I think is teaching you something about yourself that is
necessary for your soul's journey because it's like, okay, it's like a transformation,
but that's not the right word. I want to say a detour that might have been uncomfortable for a really
long time, but the out the out tour, like the actual, the outcome or the destination of this detour is
as it always is, necessary for who you know you're becoming as a person right now.
You're trying to fix communication errors with others. You're also trying to get into a different
mindset when it comes to recognition of like, hey, I did this, so I need to work on myself too.
It's not about other people all the time. And then, therefore, I feel like a lot of things
Some of it overwhelming and some of it really exciting but also it's having a hard time
letting go of the past who you were in the past and some of the things that came with
it.
And it's like nostalgia, like holding onto the old but also welcoming the new and just
trying to find who you are right now in that place.
I do also feel like there's been some stuff with your family that you're trying to clear up too
But there's some people that aren't mature enough to like kind of meet you at your level right now
And that's okay because you're going through an ascension and you have to hit rock bottom or dark night of the soul
In order to do that it comes from trauma loss pain experiences of the dark. It's okay
You're doing an okay job. I feel like just keep doing what you're doing and keep working at it
Make sure you don't lose yourself because I know that that like can fall into like addictions or bad
thought patterns or like like psychologically and human behavior wise this is just normal.
It's like a vice right a comfort blanket if you will but I feel like you're trying to find or
replace those things that were not working for you or hindering your growth in the past
and applying it in a different way or different tool so that you can do it in a positive way so
that you can grow from it and actually learn from it and then you can teach others does that make
I don't think I need cards, but I can I can pull one for you. There. I just wanted to prove to you
I don't need them, but if I'm wrong I'm wrong
That makes a lot of sense though
All right, then we're not doing a card there you go
Yankee it's okay. That's so my that's my boy. I like that though. That's it. That's on some real shit though
honestly
Yeah
There's so much more to be learned though, you know, we learned there's still so much more we could learn so much
Yeah, I feel like we learn to the end of life, right every day every day
Not a fucking it's not like a goal. Okay, you know, that was deep. Oh, it's deep for pharmacy
But yeah, so that's my first no card reading online. There you go
That was amazing, no card
Only the chosen ones could do that
Yeah, it's been a learning journey for sure for me since I was little it was a different
It's very invasive almost it's like blah, ha ha, you know
Well, when I, when I learned about the whole thing with the horoscope and shit, like that kind of blew my mind too, because it more or less is, more or less, it tells you who you really are in a way.
But then.
Exactly.
Behavioral like personality traits and such, right?
Yep.
Because I used to be the type that used to sit there and read like the horoscopes on the daily.
on on some things it honestly like it it
It speaks some facts sometimes where it's scary like you know what I mean?
Like I'm not trying to sound like a bitch, but it's not like scary, but it's like what the fuck like
You know that or like you know like some things like like
talking about you like
Like you could be reena a scripture or you could be reena
a line of a poetry or whatever, and you think like that fucking exact words were meant for you, you know what I mean?
Like that type of...
That's signs and synchronicities, that's the divine messages, yeah, absolutely.
I'm just reading the chat, let's see, let's see.
I know that my blinds aren't properly fucking. I know it drives me nuts. I'm sorry. I can't fix it.
My cat's fucked up the string and like I will replace them. I promise don't come at me too hard. Okay, babe. Thank you
There I know
I'm really sorry. I know I can't fix them. I fucking tried. I have to get anyone
They're not crackhead blind. Well, actually they look like crackhead blinds, but I know look that's your room
That's your room. That's where you snore
No, stupid read the fucking chat
So people can peek into your room like that. That's crazy
Those are wooden
No, they're gonna fall off as you post a lot a deer to come in
Oh, no, not a deer. Oh, no, a deer with antlers. Oh, no
The wood here and Elf you got some skittles
You have to pick that blind page. It's
Fuck up if you don't let me see your house right now. I don't want to hear
Yeah, I got it with the blind bro
You so I should try to pull it and she was like no, it's gonna pull open my head and then
Now an elk is gonna come through there. God. He's right
Mundo's back
Yo, God, you know, no, no remundo to the Mundo
Yo
I'm gonna ask you I see that psyche is not around so I'm assuming you're in charge of the program going on here
No, I know that page is here
Please wasn't here. I would be in charge
No, no, she's not
She's second in command. Please. No trivia, dude. Please. I'm not fucking playing trivia. I haven't all night
Oh rude, dude. That shit is boring shit. Oh fucking rude
That shit makes me want to play trivia now. It's the moon
Yeah, I got a true question. What's up with pages fucking blind blood moon. Oh, is that clumsy in here?
That's the clumsy need a moment
live in person
That's a way
That's a first. My boy making a name for himself
We're before comes in the end of the terminator yeah, it's been a while it's been a while
The good page
Please no trivia
Please play trivia
No
Reverse psychology you want to do but they don't play
They go
We're many here, bro, there's no trivia here
That's for girls trivia. What year did Canada become a state?
25, 25, that's right.
I'm about to say the same year it currently is.
What year did Paige not fix her blind?
2025.
How's that for trivia?
That's cold blooded.
You see the wood line behind her?
She came through the blinds.
Pull it down.
Pull it down nice and straight, okay?
That was cool.
She can't.
Cuz it's gonna fall down
The string is gonna fall down then she has to go to fucking Canadian Home Depot
Don't break it. Hi Alex. She's gonna read you some pills next. Don't break it. Don't break it. Don't pull it too hard
You did it
Did she do it? Oh, and she did it a little bit halfway. No, you have to put it down going baby
That was that that was a fucking
No, that was a key Alex is still talking about your black feet. He's gonna talk about the blinds for like a year. Oh
I'm making a movie as we speak, the feed line movie.
Oh my god.
Are you sure you get the front coverage like this?
Cause like I don't give a fuck.
We'll just do it
Injury I still have crutches you dickhead, but this is
Of the house, you know, I'm trying my best
All right, all right, somebody say something weird about somebody
Ghost left
Oh, I don't know we're like, where are you?
He's here cuz he lets everybody wait wait a second speaking of blinds. Look at clumsy's uh curtains there. That's pretty cool. He's got the skull there
God God you started I didn't want to bring it up bro. I didn't want to bring it up
But you can't let it go. Can you?
So, yeah, look at thumbsy shit
It's like sick in a mile my man, what is this bullshit it's like I'm thinking of my oh shit
Yeah, every day over here
Every day the other day is like every day in my life
Not the same quite but
Sort of related base a little bitchy, huh? Hey, what's wrong with you?
What I'm just I'm just focused. No you I said bae bae
So what do y'all got going on?
It was all fucking jumping over here before I came on everyone was talking and
Everyone's just all you you brought that
Yeah, bro until you sink with the mile curtains and pay just fucking water curtains kill the mood
That's what happened, but I don't know what to do
Now I'm thinking
No, that's like five in the morning almost over here. So
There's no time
Too early
Catch me in a late night. That's conspiracy hour. It's too late after four o'clock. It's too late. Look at Norakow
It's too late about three fuck with me tonight. Do you want to fuck around big? That's like seriously?
I'm not having a great big, but like I don't need you to say things about me
Yeah, I think it pays me some dick. She is
With it today
I'm already knowing she's gonna rip somebody's head off in this bitch
Fuck around and flying down
You keep an old cow, I got him
Haha
I saw that, yeah, I just saw that
I got that boom
Yup
I'm Kaboomie
See, I already snatched KZ's soul out tonight
Oh, he's buried
Where did he go? He went to cry
Well, I hope he's I rather listen to Katie and set up a truly trivia, bro
I miss trivia
Is that who they were flaming up earlier was that do KZ used to like a six-hour trivia streams. Oh my god
Trivia championships
Like we're all actually such trivia masters when I go to like find questions
It's kind of difficult to find questions. We have an out trivia. Do you know?
Hey, she's being sarcastic, please read the room. Come on. Oh
Serious, I wasn't I wasn't going up when he said I was just making a statement like we are all really playing trivia
It's hard to find trivia questions
They said show feet
I don't know if he's talking to Clumsier or Paige.
So much to put a bullet in Paige in Minecraft.
What the fuck?
Why would you say that?
that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that
I'm sorry, but everywhere you go trivia follows. Who's James what's true? I
Got a trivia question Ray. Why are you so gay? Oh my god
Why are you interested
Sure, I can always use another hoe to pimp out I mean you like smoking peanuts, bro. Is it that hard?
No, I like men's assholes. I'm a pound of shit. Yeah clip that clip that shit
You know this shit ain't gonna bother me none got it. I'll say some wild shit beyond now
You made Paige leave asshole see another ghost
Wow something else
You got your wish it's an all-guide panel now
I'm sorry, but I just can't say in front of your breath. It's the source is best
Who's that
Yeah
It's crystal on the map that's not that's a monster
Not to harder
the
she probably got locked in a psych ward to crazy bitch
nah, she went to rehab
looking words right on my mouth
she's a fun crazy though
she needs mental rehab
yeah, who is this guy on bandwagon, who is this
exile ward
she used to be funny bro without like all the nasty shit
but once you look at him
mixing the nasty shit with the trolling
mm-mm
she's beautiful though, so I pardon her
Page said have a wonderful evening. He doesn't even know what you gotta say for bums
She is pretty bro, you know, I mean, I'm not gonna do that either, you know, I'm saying
How much did this you got to put on her face to be pretty though. Have you seen that bitch natural?
She ain't the worst but she's pretty goddamn bad
Come on, dude. She's 40 years old. Thank you for the win. Who's my old ladies pushing 50 and look a hundred times better than that
Yeah, you're gonna look good in that picture. I never seen it live though. Go look at my page, bro
She's live on my page. She's like chicken legs bro. His little chicken legs bones literally bones
Like after you eat the chicken and the bone and you throw it
That's just like rolling things
Yeah
It's not really about what a female looks like but I mean
Attitude makes her look a hundred times uglier. That's the whole point
Like I couldn't be around a bitch like that. I probably I've never caught a domestic case in my life
But if I had to live with that bitch, I probably would oh my god
Yo exiled one dude, I've never heard you calling before
Yeah, why would you do that? Why not just leave the residence? Why are you resort to violence? I mean art. What would you do if you had a fucking pen?
I mean if you was that ugly, I'd get it, right? Kill that ugly bitch, I'd get it buddy, I'd kill that ugly bitch.
This must be his first introduction to me. Tonight's a light night. You don't want to see me on a regular night, bro.
This is too ugly. This is too ugly. You just got to take him out.
This dude is delicious.
that's what they say
when they're too ugly bro, what are you going to do?
they have to collect their personality before I got married
you're helping humanity in a way, you're like a hero
like, I'm going to take one for my humanity team
I'm going to take one for the team
I'm going to take one of his ugly bitches up
yo, so what are your guys thoughts on the latest of the Charlie third?
it's just great you know like it was all planned I can't believe it
wasn't that like three months ago five months ago
that's what I said from the get go you had to do it in a white shirt next to it
here we go because we see our
but it was a dude with a white shirt giving that marine signal for shots you know
hey that was the sniper and I don't think it was
apart from the little big emails came out last night
I didn't see the email yesterday
no what they said
all of the
the
No
It looks like paging a little with a beard
Ghost is in the back now. I wish I had some fun. Oh, no. Oh, no
You had to speak his name. He ain't beatled you. She only got to say his name once
B to juice be the juice
Yeah, I don't want to run one if he doesn't love guy
Don't want to run stang those bro. He's a grown-ass man. It's talking about dum-dum. Well, you such a
Trust fun baby acting like he earned that money when it's like she does not have he's back puts that get asleep. He said
in the 40-year-old that fucking says dumb dumb
did they ever figure out about that uh about that plane that crashed on what happened?
yeah crashed
i know it crashed you asshole
but was there like a
of the
the
Yeah, three people died on me. Okay, and the plane in the plane. Yeah, but on the
Three three on the ground three in the plane Alex. They had a sigil or vigil vigil for people
They had a vigil
Yeah, right summer was at the big one. I saw documentary two minutes ago body and it was like three casualties. We don't
Remember
The documentary came out tonight. I mean, I don't know. I don't know what summer got. I don't know if it was one of those UPS planes
So the cargo that was on it
Yeah, they had the Ark of the Covenant down there, that's why it crashed. Exactly
Something happened. They needed that shit needed to go down. That shit doesn't happen. Yeah, that's why
Well all the machine
Something was on that plane
the
No way. No way. Did that make him leave?
What the fuck?
Saki's coat was on the plane and he buzzed.
He's just pussy as people go wild, you know?
He's just Canadian pussy was on the plane.
Is that what you're telling me?
Oh my god, it got derailed. You know what I mean?
Where the fuck happened to God, bro?
From what his days left they're a couple
That's funny. All right, so clumsy as the mic. Oh, it looks like he's showing it down a thing
Is it a shed down? I don't know it looks that way to that or it's just you me man
I mean, I just came over here to show Psyche some love.
It's been a while since I jumped on his panel and shit.
I told him I was on a jump on it the other day,
but I didn't get around to it, so.
But wherever you might be, Psyche,
I hope you're doing good, bro.
It's your time to show him love.
Let it out.
He knows, he knows, he knows.
So I'm gonna go jump my fat ass up anyways, but uh have a good night, brother
You too, man. Peace out psyche. Appreciate it